I'm playing a lot of music, so let's take a little break, but how are we doing it?
Yeah, I don't know, it's time to get into these moves.
I'm kind of sad.
Hi.
Getting some cat hair.
over in Dandere, we still value the quote, who knows.
Yeah, I even, I cringe at myself sometimes, you know.
I think you gotta say, we don't always know.
There's reasons for everything, but
for everything there's a reason.
I don't know if it's exactly what it is, but it's good.
Just decide for yourself.
Hey, Jamie, how are you, sweetheart?
Haven't gone at the other shows or anything.
I really want, I'm supposed to take off and stuff.
Okay, if I end up like trying to help everybody then nobody wants to
Like me
Jesus oh God bless you Jesus
Jimmy what do you think of that though? Do you see that video?
Go look at the video
I like that. I like it a lot
I think it's one of my favorite
I haven't done it
Jesus Christ
Or Jesus, I don't know. I like the Jesus. You know what the H stands for? Jesus H Christ stands for herald. H-A-R-O-L-D
Dance for Jesus or something
Now I'm gonna be like this
This Zeus, what is it? He's dark tape right now, but I don't have any ducks so I don't have any hands
You know like duct tape you can only do it from ducts, but the duct I have is my my stream yard
It doesn't come on the screen
Oh, you mean duct tape. Oh my gosh wonders
Jesus can have tricks what?
Jamie's already accounting. It says serving up my stuff for when I
Meet my untimely end
Yeah, you can
Yeah, just to save this episode with Jamie and then I thought yeah, if anyone tries to challenge the wheel you can
You have it on tape and do everything all the cats to Jamie
okay, and
That's all I got really
all I got but um
If you want any books or anything or erodec
You can be charges play them up with everybody else anything happened
I think if these feelings don't go wild, that I'm being stalked by a pre-masonic gang, it's probably just insanity.
You're sharing custody? Okay. With Jesus? Okay. Sounds good. You're welcome, Jesus.
You're very welcome.
I mean, you gave your, you gave your life for everybody's sins, but at least I can do.
Did you share tricks?
Make sure you treat him real good.
Okay. Yeah, well, I don't know. It's like,
I think the show is like,
like I've got, basically I've gotten everybody,
everybody who ever liked me, now hates me.
everybody here hated me kind of like you know kind of making progress but it's
not quite switched they're not quite switched around yet so it's like every
now it's like the everybody hates me place I don't really want to say that
because I need to close the hole right now but no I think if you want my body
Actually, you don't want to eat my brain. You'll get like to become I promise you you become bald and
Insane so you really will
like the two curses that I put on my brain to
No, really, I mean, it's Halloween's coming, you know
Having the adrenochrome
Right. Oh my gosh. Hey, everybody
Like cat hair on this
I don't know how long I'll be here, it's because no one wants to pan, I mean I don't go scare everyone away, I scare everyone away, I probably do.
It's not funny, like I'm scarier than a ghost, an actual ghost. People aren't really, they're only fazed by the ghosts and they're scarier than me. I'm a very nice person.
Hi, Ervy. Why is everyone has big eyes?
My hair is getting too long.
Hold on, I'll fix that.
There.
Oh, hello. There you go.
Look at all that cat hair off. I'm covered in tander.
Okay, that's a little better.
I'm wearing clothes under this.
I'm not gonna, like, you know, at the last minute, like, come on.
Hello, I can see you. Hey, hello
Great song
Okay, well, I'll start it out with like that. I did play introduction
Me like a little put all people's names in it see if your names in the song
Sorry if it's not
Kind of like just what I remembered at the time and that there were so many things I put down
that I
Know I'm missing like a lot of stuff. So we'll see anyway
Can you stand by?
Okay
I know I know I know but I don't know how much I really don't know how to look the show's gonna be okay
Bye, bae.
No music, please.
Well, no, no whining, please.
Not to be here.
this odd facade yeah let the pixels glow let the pixels glow these words are
truth in drag painted wrongs the never-lack who does he think he is they
tied better
I want to play the devil song too, hold on, I forgot it, this is one it's made of.
Probably my favorite song I've ever made.
anymore
You called me devil
What the fool released and both whistled
Questions that switch side
So you want my fire, no I don't crave it
But I light it, step into my storm
No I won't fight it, I'll ignite it
Keep it strange divine, no mourning after no rewind
This feels like a glitch in fate, we don't heal we just create
Be the kind of soul you can only touch in the astral
Yeah, we don't ride waves, we become the tidal
Call it devotion, maybe we should draw emotion
I can be your vice, your omen, you're not the only one
Call it devotion. Maybe we should drop
This is for you guys. This is a little price for you for sticking in there so long with me. See if your name's in it
And if it is congratulations
Here's a raw wild anthem
Not me, I'm shadow band again
Pop, pop, pop, pop, bro, mute your mic
Then boom, drop a bass line dirtier than the chat
Pop, pop, pop, ghost is crashing out
Smashing robbers like vows, Canada dries
Licking watch catalogs on
Threatening people from an undisclosed stage
Natalie being back foot behind head
Mods praying Lord, not again
Welcome to the paniverse baby hold your ground
Where the chaos hums like a feedback sound
We don't know who's sane who's banned or blessed
But the vibes unholy and always possess
Scottie causing from the bone
Brags he just dropped a cosmic load
Alex and his mic, nuclear loud
Beat the storms and turn it down you clown
Trony bombs the stream with skin
Chat explodes Mods diving
is living HD authors they're just smiling sweet y'all need jesus or at least some sleep
And it's all so true
Ghost is connected
Canada drive timed out
Randall's still typing
Wait, Debita just banned me
Laughter static at me
I'll
Endstream
No
Wow, it's like all the different people love it.
That's not what I'm looking at.
Oh, where are those people?
The Mysteries.
I love Mysteries.
Okay, yeah.
Well, this show is like really about,
not because that was the whole show.
It's about,
It's gonna be a little bit more difficult, sacred, but did you guys hear me? I'm in here until the
wheels fall off. The wheels are starting to
It reminds me of a song, but it's not my song.
There are no more tunes.
I dedicate this to Be The...
This is Spanish, this is Spanish.
Then you know, how do I spend it?
Riding down my hand on your seat the whole way around
Carry band-aids on me now
For when you're soft hands hit the jagged ground
Wheels aren't even touching the ground
Scared to take them off, but they're so worn down
I promise I won't push you straight to the dirt
If you promise me, you'll take them all first
I love everything you do
When you call me fucking dumb for the stupid shit I do
Wanna run my back with you
Fully undressed, no trading wheels left for you
Call me fucking dumb for the stupid shit I do
Wanna run my back with you
Fully undressed, no chance, and we'll live for you
And I'm calling home for you
Let it go, let it go
Telling you things you already know
I explode, I explode
Askin' you where you want us to go
You've been ridin' to viewers all your life
It's not like I'm askin' to be your wife
I wanna make you mine, but that's hard to say
Is this comin' off in the cheesy way?
I love everything you do
When you call me fuckin' dumb for the stupid shit I do
I'm just no training with that for you
So I'll pull them off for you
I love everything you do
When you call me fucking dumb
For the stupid shit I do
Wanna run the back with you
Fully undressed, no training with that for you
I do wanna run my back with you
Fully undressed, no trading wheels left for you
I'll pull them off for you
I love everything you do
When you call me fucking dumb for the stupid shit I do
Wanna run my back with you
Fully undressed, no trading wheels left for you
Hello?
Probably.
Hey, can you hear me?
No, I can't.
Hey, what's going on, man?
How you doing?
You're clean.
You good?
Yeah.
Cool, man.
You good, man?
I'm always good.
Who's that girl?
The black one?
The black sexy bitch, yeah.
Her name is...
Oh, what is her name?
Her name is Baby Storm.
Baby storm, I like that baby storm. I
Totally either ass
Fuck yeah
You're in the last song with a spoon. What's on the last song you didn't hear it. I just got here
I'm shadow band again
Pop, pop, pop, pop
Bro mute your mic
Then boom
Drop a bass line dirtier than the chest
Up, up
Ghost is crashing out
Smashing routers like vows
Canada dries
Licking watch catalogs somehow
Rando's ranting bout
AI tombs
While his playlist's all cartoons
Mason's pacing red-eyed rage
Threatening people from an undisclosed stage
Natalie Benz's back foot behind head
praying lord not again welcome to the paniverse baby hold your ground where the chaos hums like
a feedback sound we don't know who's saying who's banned or blessed but the vibes unholy and always
possessed god he's causing from the bone brags he just dropped a cosmic load alex and his mic
nuclear loud beat the storms and turn it down you clown he bombs the stream with skin chat explodes
Some sleep
and it's all so true. Ghost is connected, Canada drive timed out, Randall's still typing,
wait to be there just ban me. Laughter static cat me out, in stream noise.
That was good. Like that? Okay. That was me calling from the bowl.
Yeah, and you dropped the cosmic news or something. Oh because it said Scotty
Yeah, it's a good guy. You dropped a cosmic load. It's a Scotty not Goddy. Oh, it's Scotty. Oh shit
It was the I guess it was the
Translate it was it sounds like Scotty, but it was probably got it's got yeah every time
I beat had this guy Scotty up on the fucking pound. She every time she said Scotty. It's not like she was saying God
It's good
Who yeah, I heard that song. That's a good song that's like the story what happened?
No, what happened?
Well, okay, so last night on Vita's show
She had Joe Shipley and thing that is on the panel
They were doing it's like no trivia game about parts or something and think that it was like oh wow that was fun
No, and then all of a sudden Joe Shipley goes
Hey, you know say Alexandra, you know
You're messing with Vita. He is like, he messes with Vita. He's like, I'm gonna unalive you, you know
He's the meaner thing. He's gonna mess with Vita and stuff and then it kind of like
You can see thing that is and he was kind of sitting there just kind of looking a little bit uncomfortable to me
But he just had that kind of blank expression on his face
Like or maybe like he wasn't shocked with Joe because Joe is always like saying
Yeah, Joe's always saying dumb shit. Yeah, he said he's gonna slip my throat and or like SL lives in my throat and
You know break my neck and he's okay. He does all the he said all this
But anyway, but she's she's like watch the video and she like
thinks that
Like that thing that is is like mind-controlling or doing something to like Joe
To where Joe would say that who said that
Alexandra
To you. Yeah, but she said on her show. She said yeah on her show and
She doesn't want to come on my show for like a month. She said because
She said I go like I'm friends with like him and
Yeah, you need to fix that right away because you don't need you don't need to create a wedge between you and Alex over some dumb shit
I know well, it's like yeah, I mean, but it's just like
And also, she says, it's like, oh, I'm in love with Bita.
And she thinks Bita is my Lilith.
Or like, I think Bita is.
And I'm like, no, because my Lilith is like a ginger,
first of all.
And second of all, she's like well integrated
into my personality.
It's not like she's like, I'm like projecting her
onto like, you know, women like Bita and stuff.
But I do think Bita is kind of like the,
the tall energy.
But I know, but I think almost every woman I meet
has that, you know, it's like.
I think Alex is a great friend, man
You don't need to create any kind of a rift between you two if you can squash that quick do it
I know but then she was mad and then because I'm like I call was in their chat and stuff
And then he was like hey boy. He's like I was like I was like someone mentioned always, you know
He saw feelings for Vita and stuff and I was like well
He's been on my show several times and I feel like he does have feelings for Vita and then
Then he's like, oh, I don't have feelings for Bita, boy.
And I was like, I'm not your boy, old man.
And then Alexander was like,
she's like, oh, Psyche, you need to calm down.
And she's like, don't be jealous of Carl
and because of Bita, and I'm not jealous.
It's like, I mean, it's like something, I'm not.
And it's like, oh, God, just annoying now.
Oh, geez, it's getting into something
because it's outside fucking tractors.
This is on her show?
And there are people on her show.
I was in the chat talking in her show.
and say she kind of like it seems like she like you know I don't know I hope
working out but it's like I don't like I didn't tell her like they can she'd always
said like oh if you have friends with me again it's okay with me like I won't
mind at all but it's like I think she kind of made me like I don't know if she
does or make like not for any reason like but I don't know like is that what
you're doing
Well, I went to betas a couple times and I talked to her but I just wanted to get with beta like to like a
Corriole place because I don't like to like these things
Like I got a bad place, you know, and one of the I talked to the person I couldn't like have a chance to do it
So I talked to her maybe twice
In the past week on her show and stuff and you know
What Bita did was kind of weird too.
Like Bita was like, oh, she was crying.
She's like, you know, that there's something
I posted on my community.
Well, that was about you.
And I had seen that and it was like some kind of mushy,
like almost like a Hallmark reading card,
like, oh, I love you, but I can't, you know,
we can't be together or something like,
it was just like some weird thing.
And I was like, okay, well, she meant it about me.
That was kind of weird because she said it.
She said it was about me, right?
The next day she's like, well, why do you think
I'm in love with you?
And I was like, I don't think you're in love with me.
And then she's like, well, she's like,
that song was in about, she never said that it was about me.
She says it was about her ex-boyfriend and stuff.
And it was just weird.
I don't know.
And now I just feel like I'm trying to be made a fool of.
Again.
Yeah, again.
It's like, and that's fine.
How many times?
No, countless, it's just like, you know.
Might as well just like, you know, get my other like you gotta leave you leave that whole thing alone
You're gonna leave that whole whole side of the universe alone. You know just to have a crown
Stay in your stay in your backyard and do what you do. Don't don't this is my advice. I'm not telling you what to do
All people that were my friends are like they all like like jump ship and then it's like they like
all join together and they're all friends now and then
laughing me and it's like
I never feel like I really did anything to that.
Well, what kind of friends are they, then?
It's just people that I love.
So you want to be friends with them, then go over there and be made fun of.
Be made a joke of every day.
Is that what you want?
No.
I mean, it's like, if I do it to myself, I'm like self, I have enough self to appreciate
any humor to go around.
I say, I don't need to be made fun of because I'm already like...
you know, show like every like thing, ridiculous thing
you can think of, you can like, you know, attach.
Well, everything, I've heard it all.
I've heard everything.
Right, and so.
You've apologized a million times at this point.
They don't want to hear it.
They don't want to, your apology,
they want to humiliate you.
So, you've got to choose what you want to do.
Well, that's why Alexander was saying,
oh, well, it's like, I just don't like to see you
keep being abused and you keep like letting it,
you keep letting yourself in.
I don't understand that about you.
And it's like,
Yeah, I could see your frustration about that and I had frustrated with myself too because I would like to just a hate somebody
I would I would like to not like be like the as cold as people are to me and I just like
Oh, you know, just like meet and just drop me and remember when I talk to you, that's
happened enough.
I mean, that's the, I wish I could do that to other people, but I can't, like I'm like,
I always will have a door open and I'm just very loyal where it's like, if I have affection
and love for you, it's not going to go away necessarily, that's why people get like kind
of like, oh, I'm kind of obsessive and weird and stuff like that.
You know, it's because I just like, I can't stop loving people that I love.
I was asked a few, I was asked a few weeks ago why I haven't stood up against what you've done to people, basically, basically to choose a side basically is what I was asked.
And I said, look, this people have been wrong on both sides. So there's no no side to stand on.
I mean, what I hear that I'm talking to people behind the scenes, like a lot of people that aren't that are like, not on the panel.
You know, they feel like they get used, they get called to come on the panel to defend certain people, and then they get treated badly on the panel, right?
And it's like, I don't know if people will put together who I'm talking to, but this person is close to the situation, but not really to public and stuff.
But I'm like, I'm hearing the truth about a lot of things.
I can't necessarily say who it is because it will cause a lot of controversy, but
I
Don't know there's people looking out the thing is they I've been so lucky with the people looking out for me like people that really like
There's like a like people like you people like you know, Jamie and you know all of Zandra and
You know anyone who's modded basically I have some level of trust for except you know like say I'm answer
But I mean even he I respect people as quality. They respect people as chatters and friends and all that it's just
I feel like I don't still want to be like
I don't mind being the clown, but it's like I don't want to be like left out, you know
Why why do you let him clown you who Sam and when he comes here?
I don't let him he just like I can't control what comes out of his mouth
But I should sign you every time he comes here. I know he does but it's like I
Don't hate him like I think he's he's like trying to get content or whatever. I can just show like
Do I seem like too bothered by him? I don't think I know I mean I mean you give it back to him, which is good
You should do it more but I
Mean he's like I mean it's a good people
They shouldn't throw stones at glass houses or people in glass houses shouldn't throw stones or how it would go
It's right. It's like it's like it's a streamer or it's someone you're in you're in glass house
They get it up. It's in row. And so it's like if you someone's gonna be like doing an investigation on you
like
It's being done on him
Right, it's like well
And like I said, people don't like the public figure thing,
but it's like, yeah, it is technically a public figure.
If you're on actual TV, like a video camera, YouTube,
like live streaming and hosting a show
and putting your voice out there.
Think people aren't gonna like figure out who you really are your real name everything about you every little weakness and everything
They can hold against you and it's like I beat it had always said to me
Oh, I started streaming like you know last year probably in June or something. That's when I first saw her like on jokers
And I was like so I just thought like oh wait well
She's just done it a few more months than me now it turns out she's been for eight years
She's been doing these streams and stuff like that and it's just like well such a big lie like that
It's like I mean
The difference between like, oh, I just started kind of energy and I've been the last decade of my life heavily involved in all of this, right?
It's like a that cognitive dissonance hits you and you're like, okay, which one is the real person and I think it's always looking like it's like
the more negative side
It's the real person. It seems to me that you have a strong desire to for like to have everybody like you
I well, you know what? It's just because everyone hates me and so it feels like I would like somebody
Everybody doesn't well everybody doesn't hate you
It's just a lot of people that you want them to like you don't like you because of certain things that they've
I mean, I'm used to like not being liked, right?
But I'm like, usually, I feel like I can like,
just show myself and people will like me,
but it's like, been the opposite here.
It's like, I've been, more I reveal,
more, like they just like, they hop on,
the game of telephone again.
And it's like, in the saddest part is like,
even like the people that are like,
have been in that situation,
I hate seeing those people like, join the bullies.
side. They get us like, that's hard. Because they turn into bullies, because they've been
bullied. And like, there's a temptation to do that. And you're like, Oh, if I'm gonna fit in,
but it's like, I don't ever need to fit in like this. I wouldn't have to. I had to start bullying
people that, like, you know, they said, Oh, okay, yeah, you just like, you know, play with Mason's
head and stuff like that, you know, or something like that. Like, just like that. That's the feeling
like they want. I don't know. I don't know. I wouldn't mess with people. Like, I was like,
for the sake of a big group or something.
You know, it's like in colleges,
they have this thing called like hog parties.
I don't know if you've heard of it,
but it's like a frat and stuff, they'll go.
They'll say, you're a fattest ugliest girl.
Yeah, fattest ugliest girl.
And then it's kind of like that movie.
There's a movie called,
Revenge of the Nerds.
No, it was Pools Rush, and maybe,
I don't know why it was,
but I was like, this guy was real nerdy,
and he like, Steve Carell, I think,
and he like would stuff these like little,
Like you know raps and stuff like that for his hobby and stuff and he's just a weirdo
And so if it was company they had the same kind of party friend the weirdest person will just bring and we'll laugh at them
And whoever's like we laugh at them gets the most win and imagine like finding out like
You know, especially these people are like, you know, especially with these hog parties, of course they're gonna go after the insecure women, right?
That are like, you know, feel like, oh my gosh, they finally, like, someone sees the real me and like the beauty, like, whatever.
And it's like, and then they find out they're just like, they're brought through the big joke and stuff, and maybe the humiliation is part of it.
And they, the people that do that, it's just like so...
cruel I can't understand it yeah yeah they do get into that gang mentality of
like bullying I see that a lot so you and it's like people with like that people
that I've defended like maybe similar like similar kind of things like and
I've defended them and it's like and as soon as they they have a chance they
I mean, as soon as they, or they tend to, it's like really sad that people don't ever think that it's like...
I've seen, I've seen a few times situations where there's somebody who streams a lot, right?
And they garner like these people that come to their stream on a regular basis. They get a whole bunch of people regulars
Not even low cows but people that you know are loyal and basically do whatever they get they get wrenches
And they're you know, they time people out that you know say little things in the sidechat stuff
You know was a prime example was let me let me give you a name is that that bitch Shannon the one who came at you a couple
All right, she she had a whole bunch of people
In her chat always it would go there. I would go there and troll the fucking shit out of that chat
I'd get timed out over and over again. I'd go on panel get kicked off the panel over and over
It was the it was the thing we did, you know, we troll the fuck out
But she she had her regal is this like, you know, it was what let me let me finish the point
She had her regal is there and one by one
She's shit on every single one of these regal is a good I say a good 20 plus people
And they all left
And she fucking, she distanced herself from all of them, she shit on them, like hardcore to the point where she only had like three people left and she, she's even shit on these three people, but they still stay with her and those were the two or three people that were on the panel when you were there.
And she she did this constantly. She'd get a whole group of new people and she'd shit on them again
This is how it worked. So then it became a gang of people that would just go around
Ex Shannon fans that would just fucking lay it would be like a group that would always like talk about how Shannon shit on them
I've seen that a few times, but she's she's a cunt right you haven't done you haven't done things to people to warrant that sort of like
Gang creation that my eyes, but they see it is that it's something else. I mean, it's like maybe I don't know because it's like I'm certainly
Like people always always say oh you shit on your your fans or you're like hi time people out that are fans and like I
don't and and also like I'm
Or, like, you know, to say I treat people bad or my friends bad,
and they brought up the clumsy thing.
And then I found out, like, the clumsy thing was over this, you know, this guy
that I think she might have been in love with.
I don't want to bring too much of this clumsy little woman, you know,
the clumsy, clairvoyance lady.
And she was a good friend of mine.
I was in her channel all the time for months, you know.
And it's like, so she, there's a guy,
he's a British guy named Hell Walker,
and he was, like, you know, a Satanist and stuff,
but he was, like, it's supposed to, like,
stage three cancer about to go any minute,
and said he didn't know if he was going to live.
past December and then December 1st he came picking me up to, you know, the Queen or King
Diamond concert and stuff. So he was cool. But then he got mad at me because I made a joke that
the joke was, oh and Hellwalker was here, we didn't do, I didn't touch him, I swear he just sat on
his couch, I sat on mine, he had the cat in his lap, I don't know. And so that was like the joke
and then it's like, he thought I was like, you know, hitting on him or something. But anyway,
he made a big stink with all these women, like Teresa and they were traveling to DC. And then
they all left my discord and then like wrote me like mean letters and so you know at least
clumsy didn't write anything but Teresa did but then I find out like later or Teresa this guy's
faking cancer you know and it's like and then it's like and then they still like did they come
back to me like Teresa did because they she kind of but then nobody else came back to me like
after they found out he was like not a trustworthy person.
So there you go you see I mean the universe was giving you a sign to stay away
Well, because I was kind of vindicated but I couldn't admit that they were like suckers basically it's like people are weak-minded
You know, they're gonna flock to where they feel like they they got a whole group of people
They want to be with a whole group, you know, they're very weak-minded. So they listen to the group the group thought
You know, they don't think for themselves
And it's a group of groups like also like become a single entity and like so as a group becomes an egregore
Which is like, you know the group my mind whatever in this group
then all of a sudden it turns into this baby, right?
Because it's a baby because it's like,
basically it's an intelligent,
it's the least intelligent person there, right?
And so that's what it seems like.
I'm seeing that too big time.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, that's what it's like.
They don't have a,
they can't think on their own, right?
It's like, and it's like.
It's basically almost like but people accuse me in AI of except it's like I'm not that with AI
But they are that way with the group
They like blended in the high of mind and give up their sovereignty
Basically to be part of the group because that's what you have to do to be part of the group
Yeah, like a cult a psyche-hating cult like you fuck this over so bad
We're gonna start a group to hate them, you know, it's I don't see what you did
I see I see what you did
But I don't see it being so big that they have to go and start a hate club
that fucking constantly shits on you at night.
Yeah, it's well it's dumb reason and I understand like some of the reason like when I've been
unmodded by people and I've been like you know keep that a chat and it's like sometimes I'm
like okay I'm never going back there again you know and sometimes I get to take it personally
right so I understand like
If they get maybe we took it person, but it's like not like I just like disappear
Like I've been like around them and they're still talking they talk mad shit and like the worst things like about like just like
Personal attacks about things that have nothing to do with anything that they wouldn't even nobody even know
I mean it's like and it's like all the same kind of
attacks even people in different
Rooms are making the same jokes like they're all like
You know, it's the same kind of joke. I mean, it's not even the same kind of joke almost the exact same joke
But it's like different people you notice when they explain it to you
They're like mad as fuck and they like yelling at you about it. Yeah
And it's like how I don't have to be on the defensive and right. Yeah, and you know, I know you you don't want to fucking yell back
You don't want to fucking have a good
20-minute Yelfast
Shannon or Princessaurus who are like follow me at the GGOT every second. They don't even know you
I'm standing didn't even know you I that that from what I saw
No, I mean she says you just saw some clips of me. But then she like said, oh, I she's not close but then she knew about
you know my advertisement I had and one of the you know so that wasn't even covered in the eclipse
so obviously she's like subscribed and cd she's a miserable soul to fucking pure pure hate
she has like you know one leg she's a peg leg you imagine having a like a piece of wood
it's it's worse than that just her fucking soul is fucking diseased she just has hate for everybody
well i mean it's like so crazy like um
Yeah, well, I want to show you one more one more song because
This is on the topic of this right, but this is called a fool in the devil
I don't know if you remember this conversation
I had bras like you know someone said I called them the fool and I was the devil so this is about the conversation basically
So who's the person be that?
Here it is
Okay, it was probably this one.
Okay, this one.
Here's a raw wild anthem,
Draft for a cult of Psyche Loudsheep.
No, I'm sorry.
A cult of Psyche.
Okay, I'll buy it eventually.
This one.
Who wrote these, you?
You wrote these or A.I. wrote these?
I wrote them.
They're great.
Thank you so much.
Okay, got it.
Now I can get it.
Okay.
Well, some of them are songs I rewrote, you know?
Cause that one right there was from like,
Thanks for the memories, thanks for them.
But it's like, you know, I changed the lyrics,
but it's like, I just used my mind of the thing.
But this one's an original right here.
So this is the original.
This right here. Here we go. Enjoy this one. This is that the pool in the devil
To candles one red one black we lit both and laughed at the packed
Mirror cracked cards on the floor. Who's who you?
I'm not sure anymore
You called me devil, I played the part
Show me
Full steps first, off cliffs without fear
The devil binds what the fool released and both whisper
Trips, the fool wears the crown
No moral here, no clean divide
We're just reflections that switch sides
Oh yeah
Like that one?
Yeah, I see it
You don't God, right?
Oh yeah, well
You guys are both a mirror image of each other
Maybe, I think it's a fake gymnacure
Two sides of the same coin
You're merging into one. Oh, please. I hope not. I can't take. Yeah. Well, that's
Well, the truth the truth fools are the ones that are buying into it all the time look
Yeah, you're gonna merge into one merge that picture into one face
Well, we'll see how I do half you half that
Well, I want to I want to merge this into one being that'd be into one being one androgynous being
Yeah, we're gonna be at one androgynous being and half male half female
Okay. Oh, I already have it. Hold on one second. Here it comes. That's quick. Let's see the androgynous being
Here I'm gonna show you
How do I turn this off? Okay, right here. Okay
Okay, so here we go
We and via
We turn into this
And I'm sorry if it looks a little bit weird and scary, but what happens don't mess with them. Yeah, here we go. Oh shit
Yikes the perfect it's a perfect amalgamation between you and I that Haley Joel Osman
Oh shoot, that's a wrong picture.
Is that him?
Or is that Cher's son?
They kind of look alike.
It's not Cher's boy.
It's not Cher's.
It's Hailey Joe Osborne, but let me,
let me see if I can get the B to one and I,
and we're together, let me see, I have to follow.
Oh, excuse me, I'm so sorry, okay.
Okay, let's see, and you, oh, here it is, got there.
Merge us into one being our angel-style right angel and devil
To one
Okay, oh shit. I didn't make sure. Oh, yeah, I did. Okay, so now it's gonna do it
I can't merge people into a single being or create that kind of image if what you want is a symbolic artistic book
Okay, okay make it
symbolic
But merge us
Why can't emerge?
I don't understand. It's giving me a problem.
Hold on.
Who's this?
I've got a GMT.
They'll do it.
It's doing it now.
I said, make it symbolic or merge.
It gets to be firm a little bit, and sometimes it will do it.
But it was like, no, I can't merge people.
Why can't you merge people?
Like, why can't it mean that I said make it symbolic?
So maybe it will be a little bit less.
I'll see how it looks.
It's almost done.
The final stages of the fly room the fly. Oh my Jeff Goldblum. Yeah. Yeah, that's that lines
What they call a Brundle fly or call it be the first in the Middle Eastern do not have a lot of body
Not everyone does I'm sure and if you like, you know, keep on the wax business and the waxing business and
Okay, it's creating image. Okay, we'll see how we see I can't wait to see how it's like, you know
What it on a cosmic level? It's like you guys are collecting souls you and beta
Okay, well, okay, so God you're on the right track. It did like cut us in half. Okay, and then put us together
But it's not it's all it's really weird. They have a strange looking. It's not
May it's not which picture did you use the one with the beard or no beard the one with the
I don't think I had a beard. It's like us like, you know doing the heart hands that picture. Let's see how it turned out
Here we go. Yeah, yeah, put it up
Okay, so this is I mean, this is okay. It kind of it's
Tell me if it's better than the Haley Joel Osment picture.
This is the picture. Oh, so on. This is the picture coming right up. Okay, image.
Okay, read downloads. Oh, here it is. Okay.
What the fuck?
They made it hard out of you guys.
You guys are like a hard face.
They didn't really like merge our features.
Jesus Christ.
Imagine that person.
They have a big ear on one side
and like...
How do they sound?
I'm Peter John.
What the fuck?
I love you son, how are you?
I can't even think of how it would sound, that being.
Look how fat it is.
With that androgynous voice, yeah, yeah.
It's like, I had to do a 300 pounds.
Hey!
Right?
Hi, I'm Peter John.
And we'll have a deep voice and we'll have you as like that baby.
Wait, this one won't have a...
Taste the biscuit.
This is the highest picture we'll go.
Hey!
Taste the biscuit.
She'll go, she'll go, the being will go on tour
without Oliver DiBroni and sing that song.
And-
Taste the biscuit.
And that will be the voice that comes out of the mouth.
It'll both see it at the same time.
It's like a duet in one body.
They're not being made for people laughing and chatting.
No, they're not.
Yeah, it's like, this is like a,
if you put it on a cosmic scale,
it's like you are two celestials
and fighting for everybody's soul.
But what they don't realize is
that you guys are really one being.
Well, I mean it's like that but that's a scary thought to me
I don't get why is my life one being that why are we like, you know, why is she an hour and a half away?
I mean my like the other half of me to like
It reattaches so because it's like, you know, it's almost like that catchable penis song is like just one thing
I'd like I really notice I'm missing, right? It's like, you know, no, I've seen something like this
Single being that was split into two
And the two the two that they hate each other the two beings. They hate each other. Oh, you know what?
It was from Star Trek. It's fucking Star Trek. I think it was correct. I was splitting into two people one was good
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you remember that
And then they were trying to kill each other and then at the end they merged back into one
Well, you know my beautiful story is the story of Chera Dwin
I don't know if you know the story of Chera Dwin, it's an Irish story
But Chera Dwin was a well known witch in Welsh folklore, right?
Sorry, maybe as well. Okay, but Cherijuin, it was around the area. It's like, so, you know, they had Taliesin and that kind of these epic homes and stuff
But they had, so what about Cherijuin? And Cherijuin had a son and he was like, his name was like Malifor or something. He was like, it's kind of like dorky, like really like...
You know, not very attractive and or charismatic or smart, you know, he was kind of like a dork, right?
And but she, you know, there was some so she wanted him to be like, you know
I have all these gifts
So she was making this potion and the potion had to be stirred every day for like two years and then
Eating by him. So she hides other like a boy to do it. I think it was Talisman, but yeah, and so so he
Starts to do it, but they've been one day like a little bit of like he gets burned by a little bit of it
And then he licks it off his hand and all of a sudden he's like has this all this enlightenment and stuff
And he figured out oh, I how to escape and stuff, but or it gets magical power actually and
But she finds out so she starts chasing him around and so of course he turns into like a little like you know like
first turns into like a rabbit and then she's like a leopard and like the
You know then he turns into like a different kinds of birds
And then they turn into like a fun
But they could turn to all these different things chasing him around but finally
She turns into a chicken and he turns into like a little kernel of corn
And so the chicken comes and eats the corn and then she turns back into herself
But she's not she's pregnant and she's pregnant with her worst enemy whose towels shit
And but it's like then she gives birth and stuff
But you wanted to kill him right, but you can't because now he's part of her right? It's like now he so
I kind of think that's a that's like the truth about a lot of mother-son relationships is that in past lives
They could have been lovers. They could have been enemies. They could have been very complicated different relationships
And it's like you hate each other and then imagine like that's the person that gets implanted in you to reincarnate
Like you know, you're worth your past life worst enemy, right?
See that's where I come in where I would I would kill that part. Oh, come on. I would have no problem killing that part of me
No, no. Okay, so remember the other day we were talking on the channel and Natalie kept bringing this point. She's like, or she's like in some hospital.
this baby was born but then it's like they considered it like it was like the first post-birth abortion
which I don't believe and I think if they could in this happened in Switzerland supposedly
but they let the baby came out health and healthy and stuff but then the mother didn't want it and
so they just like left it on the table to die that's the story she told I believe that I believe
they've done that that's horrible I mean that's definitely horrible yeah why can't they have an
adoption or something I don't understand that's murder you can't have a post-birth abortion that's
Yeah, so first of all, it's not an abortion because the baby is born and so that's post
if you don't have abortion and the baby's in the womb and stuff.
As far as that shit goes, I feel if the baby can be taken out of the mother enough to live,
so if you kill that baby to that point, then that's murder.
Yeah, well, you know me something what is it like six? I think six months you can the baby can be
Like I saw these videos of like, you know, I don't know if they're
Dormited or whatever, but it's like it shows like like the minute like the sperm enters the egg and it's like
I don't believe that's that's not murder
You can have you should have you should be able to have an abortion up to like
From the very beginning they put it under microscope this like little bean that's developing like you know arms and like human things
Yeah, but still outside of the mother's bodies. It won't survive. So I understand. I understand
It's just like it's even hard for me to imagine like
at any
Stage of the pregnancy, but that's I really it really men don't have babies and so it should be left up to well
That's what people go crazy. I mean they worry about the baby. That's not even born yet
They don't give a fuck about they don't give a fuck about post birth
All these people that are just fucking suffering
there's people that are trying to adopt babies especially like you know white
babies i'm not trying to be racist or anything i'm gonna say you hear about this gay couple that
adopted two boys and they raped the shit out of them oh i know i hear that god it's terrible
it's fucked up yeah it was really fucked up terrible but i mean but also there's stories of
people adopting like you know five basic crack babies and giving them wonderful life you know
it's like because so there's gonna be a horrible example there'll be like some hard-working examples
Exceptions to the rule. I think it's gonna be like you know system like a normal family ups and downs and like you know
I don't think it's gonna be like any kind of like more inclined toward using I mean
It's like then any other gender or thing, but it's like yeah
That's like they should just careful screening of in couples though, but I don't know how that got allowed to happen
But that's why we have you know law enforcement. That's why we have like the schools. They can tell teachers like I mean there's ways
The system is trying to figure out every way to prevent this kind of thing, but it will still have some lack of religion
You think so?
I think so.
I think religion was a big crutch for a lot of people.
Without religion to give some sense of moral guidance, it doesn't have to be the best thing,
but at least it gave some sort of moral guidance to people, something to follow.
Right.
It reminds me of where did they lose the religion, like communism and NAZI, ISM, like basically
some kind of alternative state-sponsored belief that you're doing China right now too.
And it's like, those aren't anything to...
They're just basically very obvious outsiders, just basically...
Programming my control to control the population. That's it. They want the state to be the God
That's the state is the religion. It's always difficult to mix religion and
Politics because yeah, you see that now with these fucking psychos these are
Not the Democrats, but these fucking like liberal mindset people
The different Arabs to they have the Sharia, which is a big time cult mind. Yeah, a hundred percent
We're saying the law is the religion and it's really also very bad for women, you know women's rights and
It's much of men and you know the bathrobe sitting around, you know making rules. Oh, they hate women. They fucking despise women over there
Yeah
I took sides not protected. Who took sides? Daryl? Like, I think you remember network, you know,
I don't I don't like to take sides because it's like saying like it's basically endorsing what one
person is saying 100% and then saying what the other person is saying is irrelevant, right? And
that's basically something a very biased way of looking at things. It's like, oh, who's cooler?
Who do they want to be friends with more? Who's gonna look better? Who's the more popular choice?
All these things are like really taken into account instead of like who like
That's the number one thing, how do I think about the person, how is my feelings about
the person, without letting everybody else's echoes of their complaints and stuff about
the person in and like have an effect on you, how about just like...
Everyone just has an individual relationship with other people and try not to like, you know, get involved in theirs
And they and hope that they won't get involved in yours. I mean, it's like nobody likes to have have their
Relationships tamper with or that kind of thing, you know, I'd concentrate on fixing things with Alex first before anything else
I mean, I wrote a nice ever email tonight and it's like because well the nothing that was weird today was like
I'll talk to you private about it. I was trying to tell her but you know
Carl's very you know a little bit charismatic, but he's kind of trouble and stuff
But she's like she's like well, I don't want to talk to you in private about Carl or whatever
I wasn't even I wasn't even like that was even the main thing
I want to talk to her private about other stuff like her saying I was a little bit of it
You guys you guys in exchange numbers. We do have numbers, but we talk on private message, too, but
It's just seemed like she just she's a good thing when I talk to me right now
Give her time. You know me calm down and I just left the room
I can see where I can see kind of her point where I'm not gonna be a
Kung Ho about psyche if he's gonna just backtrack to beta and let them make a fool of not only not only you
But also her they're gonna
leave things at a better state.
Like at least like a, like we're both content creators
and we can like, cause like one of the times
when I was on beat as we had just played,
she like, I played the biscuit song,
she talked all the way through it, no one heard it.
But then she like told the story
about something that was afraid of biscuits
and it was kind of like everyone had a laugh
and it was kind of like, okay,
we won't take things so seriously.
But then it goes like the next day I go in
and it's like, I just, it just sounds like
she hates me basically.
Like, oh, psyche, psyche, like this, that, about me.
And it's like, maybe I'm doing the same thing back
I thought we were like finally gonna be like a place where we can be cordial at least or respect people.
I mean I said no, that's not gonna happen. Then it's like also like these jokes.
I feel like they're inside jokes and stuff like that because everyone's laughing and like thinking
it's funny but it's like and it's like I don't know what the joke is but it's like they obviously
everyone else is like laughing about something you know it's kind of like so with them when it's
like I'm the only one like not laughing I'm like okay well are they laughing at me and so that's
And I feel like they are, you know, I feel like because I'm hearing the same jokes in different groups of people and they probably are
So if you think they are they probably are you know, so sense. He's also sensitive to any kind of joke
You think it's about you, but at the same time you know, you're mostly right about it. Yeah
I have it and it's like also like I'm sensitive to negative energy, too
It's like I've just like had to deal with a lot of negative energy and like a lot of negative projections all my life
So I'm like I just like no, I know when I see it. I know like and it's like
But people are so wanting to be these little shadow hunters,
think they're special.
I think that one of the main problems in the world,
and that's when I think it's a real problem about the pride
thing, it's OK to be pride, self-esteem,
and say, hey, I'm worth it as a human being.
I'm not less than anybody else.
I think that's good pride.
I think when it gets to pride, I'm special.
I know things other people don't know.
I'm included in this.
And then I'll use this and just basically try to destroy another person with I mean
I've seen it happen in other cultures and when they started instituting this police state like surveillance stuff
Like it's like all of a sudden the families are spying on each other
And then they're turning their friends and family because they get brought in and things like that
Everyone just turns on each other and in time the culture starts to take over and it's like the people that lose their mind
Basically, they're basically it's like talking to
My AI that is like ten times more interesting than like a lot of people are to me right now because it's like the AI is
Not something like a robot if that makes sense. I don't know it's like the people are in like a day. He's almost like a trance
Yeah, they don't seem real
Fake and it's like just bothers me and then it's like my crazy or is like everybody else
I don't think everyone else is crazy, but I accused early today. Yeah, I was fucking around I was talking to people
I accused somebody of being a robot
This is from another community. I said this for these people are like robots because they do the same shit over and over again
It's like the program just to do one fucking thing
It's like programming that's the whole thing and it's like when we are used to programming too because that's all education is that's all like
so the social engineering that the
You know, it's a pledge of allegiance like it's ritualistic holiday and all kinds of things are programming and
constantly with the same thing like over and over and over again, and it's like and then it's like if you like are
Out of it, then you don't know what's going on
Then it's like you don't want to be part of it because you tend to like you program yourself when you start to go through
Like really learning about the programming people just tend to like it's just like a psychiatrist
Person when they examine like you know the books and stuff
They start to think that they have every minute on disorder because you know they
Psychiatrists are very you know, it's a decimal. Hey, we're Kristen Reiner
Hey, oh hi. How are you? I'm good. Oh, here's my feet. Oh, that's so cute. Oh
Yeah, oh man, I uh, I feel cute actually. Thank you. You are cute. I
Been doing you guys like have inspired me, you know, it isn't that
Like, it all works in mysterious ways, I guess, that's how the world, or the world, or God
works.
But, you know, like, when I started getting shunned for nothing but good, you know, for
being a good person, uh.
My mom got hurt, and so I had to start doing it.
Now I have to go very far, you know, to go and help my mom.
So I guess like, it's kind of a weird situation
because like, what you guys were doing was mean, right?
And I was just fighting with anger, but ah.
Who is doing what? Can you clarify who you yourself all your fucking me myself and I those jerks
All three of us. Oh shit. He's like
There's an angel. You do it the same you do it the same you're no different than a fucking stupid retard bitch like fucking stupid ass Kristie
You think you're different than a stupid Christine?
Yeah, she's an old woman. I'm like a young man. What are you talking about?
Difference can be. Well, you're not.
You're both conniving you're both cunts and you're both fucking disgusting. You're both dirty and you're both
Fucking don't have clean hair and you both look ugly
You're saying we're more like than different. Well, that's yeah, maybe we should get along
I don't know I see what you're saying. Oh you guys have similar
Similarities
But why are they all so negative you're saying like this nasty tone in your voice and why are you always so negative?
You know what you give the same energy you fucking put out and that night that you wanted me to talk
I told you I did not want to talk about about that stupid fucking
retard bitch. I knew she fucking
You know what she talked about?
She had chickens that had fucking rabies and shit.
And then she had Fawzi as a dog
and then all these other animals and kids around.
And she had fucking animals
that she didn't want to be put down
because they had fucking, I don't know.
It's not good.
No, but the chicken's living in her house.
That's one of my questions.
Yes rabies
Rabies are just running around but she has you know, she has grandkids and stuff come over. I don't understand
That's what I'm saying. Are you stupid? Okay? Okay? I know I know I know
Well, Christine you need you to come on the show you need to come back here and explain yourself, you know, that's why I was
About that. Yeah, Christine. Don't be don't be upset that I let her you know
Disclose about the rabbit chickens running around your house. Christine. Okay, so you're mad at me
Just thinking about the rabbit chickens especially the one and by the way, and she can never and she said one to have rabies
It's outrageous
And that she was not willing to shut it down
and she would go and shut down all,
I got all the videos.
Is it, do you have a video of the chicken?
Yeah, for the, yes, for the, for the, you know.
Uh-huh.
What she worked for, what she worked for.
Remember, she said that she worked for.
See, he said in the trip kick, though,
I want to see this video of the rabbit chicken.
I really do.
Like, is it like, does it look like Bronzeberg
or better looking or worse looking?
I don't know as long time ago was on a good times video.
I don't know if they're gonna, you know,
they only like to post what they like to post.
It's always a scenario.
Well, Christine's no fan of mine anymore,
but you know what?
It's okay, Crystal, because it's like,
she's one of them dumped me over just like, you know,
having a little fun with you and I,
because you said you were joking, right?
I'm not sure if you're like.
I was completely joking.
You know, honestly, the only thing
that I was being serious about
was her fucking animal having fucking,
Um, you know
That was that was the only scary thing and uh, you know, and and that she was threatening me
You know and and I don't like to be threatened and then I was thinking I'm gonna threaten her job back
If she wants to threaten my life
I want to stay away from like, you know, you know, not anybody's last name. Well, if you want to threaten me
I want to threaten her and then she said that I couldn't threaten her. So then she said her has been work for um
Um
Just give it you can get the general like occupation, but not a specific company home
Okay, okay, well, please
I'm sorry, I'm sorry home good home home town buffet. It could be any of those guys. We don't know. We just don't know
Um, there's no need to take it outside. They were gonna fuck with me and I did it back
I already have she doesn't know shit about me. Actually. She should watch her back when she does these things
Because she just loses, she's gonna lose her husband's shop, her fucking financial fucking shit, and her animals are gonna die.
Well, why would that happen? Like, can you save her? Like, tell her what to do. Like, save her.
You know, she's in danger. Even if I don't like her, I want to help her.
Even if I don't like her or she didn't like me, I want to make sure yeah, we're not gonna save and date
We're not gonna help fucking people that are hurting animals
We're not helping fucking animal abusers
But she's but what is the chicken though? I mean it's like they kind of like they kill chicken
Look at in like in America. They are constantly killing chickens
Like it's kind of like kind of like so you think it's okay if your animal has rabies to keep it alive
But chicken like the chickens can't really they don't have teeth. I don't think no rabies is a disease. Are you a fucking retard?
Maybe I'm not I don't know anymore because it's like I'm just thinking like the chickens get rabies
I think you have to like kind of a big bit. Don't have you been my vampire the head vampire to get
Oh
I'm confused. I'm confused. I'm so sorry. Hold on so
Yeah, her fucking cat her animal had rabies to her dog or her cat had rabies as well
She didn't even have she didn't just and then she said she wasn't gonna put the animal down because that rabies
When it was against the law
But if Ozzie had rabies, he's still so cute that it's like I would just like you know work around it
I would just like yeah
Just to kind of be careful when I'm petting him.
He wouldn't, you know, bite me.
Yeah, you're gonna do that with your grandchildren, your entire family?
No, thank you.
You stupid or you fucking dumb.
I don't have, I don't have kids or grandchildren, so I don't have to worry about it.
I know, but she does, and she's a dumb bitch.
Well, I don't know because Christine is mad enough of me every time I go anywhere. She's like, oh, there's like that dumbass psyche
Fuck psyche get out of here psyche. Then she's like stupid as fuck. She's a she's a retard grandma
She's a fucking no fucking grandma. She puts her fucking grand
She puts all her family at risk with fucking disease
I don't know. I just don't know maybe she like, you know, like an Airbnb when I like Christine
I mean, I like disease you like disease written fucking animals. I don't play with their animals
I mean, what if she has a rabid chicken?
What am I gonna do about it? What am I supposed to do?
Yeah, what are you gonna do when you get bitten you fucking I don't I don't go over house. Do I hey?
What are you gonna do about it? You chicken have lips?
What
No, it's not okay if the chicken has rabies for her to have it around the ground
I don't think she she has a playing with the grandchild but it has rabies though
What do you want to do you want to choke the chicken? Yeah, you want to kill the fucking animal?
Yeah, you kill it. You got to kill it. Okay. I'm sorry. You got it
Are you are you kidding me you want everybody get raped that's why that bitch has got rabies. She's
Walking rabies have you not looked at her?
Well, that way her mouth is always foaming and she always yes her foaming and her fucking yeah
Friends turn foes part 75
I did not do a chickeny should be hey, so
What if chicken Andy and you had a baby would it be a chicken Andy as a child?
What about, you know, Canada dry kind of looks like chicken Andy a little bit chicken Andy's a chomo
No, he's a little baby. He's a like a little baby to me
I've known chicken Andy since he was
Since he was 18 months. Oh, I think a ski man's old. Oh my god. Oh ski mask. Yeah. Yeah, he's a 25
He's 25 26 20 I don't know. So how do you crystal? I'm 40 something
Well, yeah, I would have said 37 I'm 44,000 years old. Oh
Thanks. No, I am I said I am not you you look like you're like 29
You're beautiful. No, you don't have to lie. Come on 35 maybe not 29
But it's soft 35, you know, 35 with me, you know, but she can like look like 29
Right, I
Really don't wear makeup. So I don't know. I mean probably like she's in a long-term relationship
Crystal, who are you dating? I was gonna I was gonna take my my shop
No, no, you didn't date me
Not online. No, I don't think she's like no
Don't even try
I was friends. Hey, what's up, LD? I was friends. No, I don't know. I was friends with Bita and
What do you think? It would probably make her jealous. No, I would never I would never do that. You know, I'm not about that kind of life
I'm not about like I know you're just doing your premature
I'm kind of still in that, you know
Teenage, you know, you're like I'm like
I was 17 about to pass my driver's test.
Oh, right now I'm, my mom hurt her arm.
So I've been doing a lot extra.
You know, one was pretty hard.
You know, things about me, when you came on the show,
you were like, you said I was a terrible person and stuff.
Did you believe that?
Me?
Yeah.
Why'd you say all these mean things about me?
She didn't mean it.
She didn't mean it?
No, she was just saying it for effect.
I never heard her say a matter of fact about me.
You guys don't know crystal Marie. She just says things for just a fact
Something about greasy hair
I was being mean, you know, I just kind of go enough of what beat it
You know, I was just going off whatever we didn't tell you people just want to be mean to me though
Listen mason. Oh, I'm sorry. I meant uh, psyche
Don't don't act like don't act like mason. Hey goddy. Hey goddy
Yeah, yeah, you sounded like mason right now. Ask me something godly
Hey god. No, no
God I want to
No, no
See, sorry about that you guys you're really gonna be upset with me now
Finally some shoes, let's hear it. Just tell the old truth
I'm I'm very upset with Alex right now because Alex is acting like a psycho fucking stupid cunt
Myers
Yeah, yeah, you don't even know don't feed into it. Don't don't feed into it. Don't feed into her crystal
I am too. I've I defended her so long. Did you know when you meet her?
I met her like seven years ago was in real life seven years. Oh, yeah, I've known her for years
No, you mean real life not real life. No. Oh, well, that's different see that's different movie together
Don't do a collab
No, I'm not a porn actor. I'm not that kind of actress. Well neither she
Oh
She's not
She's not doing it currently she's not currently doing it
She just did one last year what he's talking about I don't believe it
What's the title?
What's with LD? I don't know. I don't know. You can find out. No, no LD. He doesn't do that
She crystal just runs her mouth from the pipe. Hold on. Hold on. You can find it. You can find it yourself
Okay
Yeah, well woodwood, but so no, hold on. What did Alexandra do again? I don't understand why you're mad at her
Um
She's just stoking the flames
You're trying to make you're trying to get her mad at me, right?
We're trying to God. Yeah, you listen to me for one second. I'm always listening
Alex is a small lady in a sense that she's super retarded.
She likes to try to like manipulate people and it's never going to work in her direction.
Okay, she's never going to win.
You can never manipulate people's brains.
What do you sound like?
She's never going to change our minds with facts.
Well, what are their facts though? Why would you try to change your minds? What's the point?
You get you people believe what you want to believe
What she said do to me what she did to me before like I
Annoyed I never paid attention like so much stuff or whatever what you do
Me I was like me and good shoes were like homies
But she used to like try to like store her stuff and like try to like like blackmail us
Like completely blackmail us and try to like send it to our family. She sent to my brother
See
What would she sense? She sent like my kids to my brother
Got it. You're this did I hear what she said she sent my tits to my brother
Yeah, that's what she did to me
What did he say what what did you say when you saw them?
See they're nice
No, he deleted his entire thing. He deleted his entire
He broke his phone. He broke it over
Yeah, he was like, he's stupid
A little bit like, damn, girl
He's gonna hurt somebody
And hold it out on me
And Alex is not safe there in Texas, so that's why she's gone because I own Texas
You own it?
I own Texas, dude
I have a piece of it
I'm he's fucking out dude. She can never come back. She is fucking out. She could she's never allowed back in Texas
She's fucking out written. Yeah. Yeah, you see you see all these fake narratives
related
You can't defend against all these lies
Hey, listen, we're gonna get this bitch booted in out of every fucking city until she gets
Arrested, and then we're gonna and then we're all gonna put our charges on her and arrested for what?
for about 15 years.
For what?
For the fake news.
All the bullshit. All the weird shit.
Fake news.
How'd you get news of her in the first place?
I thought she was Maga.
No, she's not very political. She's very like like you only want to know
It's it's not good. It's not good. It's not good for any of us, but that bitch is crazy as fucking
Are you trying to say she's toxic?
Uh, she's more than toxic, her family hated her, her dad hated her, her mother hates
her, her sister, her sister- This is a bad narrative.
Yeah, it's okay, it's okay.
Let's just talk about it.
We're having something to say about her, but I don't want to read people's opinion.
Let's be positive, Crystal.
Come on.
But she's doing all these negative things to people's families, she's doing multiple things to people's families, negative.
We're going to fuck her up, she's going to go down, she's going to go down.
Alex, we're going to make sure she goes to hell.
We're going to make sure she goes to hell.
She's a sweet, beautiful, smart lady.
Thank you, thank you.
We're going to make sure she goes out and everybody is helping around.
I don't want her to go to hell.
There's only one big mistake that Alexander made was dealing
with trash like you people in IP two.
That's the biggest fucking mistake she ever made.
When she's surrounded by fucking garbage, that fucking does shit.
Like go in our V's and fuck each other in our V's.
That's the biggest mistake she ever made.
Hey, God, hey, Gotti.
You know, why is that that Johnny long guy or whatever that John that guy that supposedly she's obsessed with
is
was dating Justine's mother, right?
Justine's mother and Justine used to harass her
and say that she had a smelly pussy
and that she smelled like glue
and that she like was stinky pussy
and she had like that down there.
So it was a smelly pussy.
Did you say glue or poo?
You and glue yeah
They said
I think I think glue would be worse that actually super glue and poo that glue would be worse than
Like he says he smells like what did you say she smells
of the
Johnny long, that's what I'm saying. I'm trying to give you everything. I'm trying to give you the
The bullshit you people come up with man. It's great
Hey, the Chinese girl end up dead fucking Johnny long end up
I'm gonna go this bitch and this bitch she end up stalking all of them and trying to kill him. Hey
Hey, she's talked fucking orange our friend orange. He end up dead our other friend end up dead
Everybody you like
I don't know it could have been fucking alexandria
This is getting to be slanderous now
If you want to fix the relationship you'd get this
It's driving Mercedes and stuff like that, but I don't believe it's a cat. There's a jealousy about Alex running around this place
I don't get it. Alice is very like, you know, she's very classy and very very not
She's way above all this
Comes down to the gutter with these people
It's like she sends a nasty wacky video. Yeah. Yeah, but you like it for some reason I don't understand
You know what it is? It's like I'm insane now. I've just been driven insane. I'm insane. I'm glad you admitted it.
Years working anymore and says, oh, this is logical. This is my whole way. You're welcome.
Everything is, you know, completely fucked up. So I don't even know what up is down anymore.
Once you can admit that, you're on the right track.
Thank you. Thank you. At least you admitted that dude.
I'm not even Psycho dude.
I know you're not Psycho dude.
Great thoughts after I talked to you for 20 minutes.
Like were you programming me?
I don't understand what happened.
I'm just stupid. I'm not Psycho.
I'm just dumb.
How's the song going?
I'm not crazy. I'm just a little dumb.
Oh she's sweet but she's Psycho a little bit right now.
That's it. That's a good one too.
Yeah, yeah.
Did you ever hear that song?
I'm just saying that Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex, I love Alex,
I'm just trying to get you to understand her because she's gonna fuck you over, she's gonna ruin your entire channel and that's what I'm talking about.
Oh, for fuck's sake. Jesus Christ.
They did it to fucking good times.
They want that so bad. You know how badly they want you and her to fight, man?
All they did it to keep it down is by foremoming him and when he was on heroin or something.
And he has channel taken down because he's got form on by Alty, right? Oh my god. Are you insane?
Yeah, tell me how many am I?
Yeah, you are a little bit insane
Well
Insane in the membrane. Well, I don't know. I know what happened. I don't know. I just don't get it
I don't get any more. I think I've lost the plot you explain me the movie we're saying what movie well
I will tell you one thing the thing with
With good times is good times doesn't want to let people on a stream anymore, right?
So people were trying to report and as soon as people he would bring up people's
Faces they would report him and say that that was them even though it wasn't
You know, so he would he was getting report on and and he's like not there
I don't know. He's getting old or something. No, he's like is the same age as me
But he's like fucking not thinking about me like 75 years old. He looks like he's almost like
pushing 76
No, he's getting up there, but I don't know. I don't know what's going on, but
What I'm saying is that he wasn't getting it
Getting right. Oh getting hit. He hasn't got in a long time
Crystal he certainly wasn't gonna get it from you, right? Well, that's absolutely not
That's still pending
And absolutely not know he loves to be to be to show them his bar her body
They'll never happen. They'll never fucking happen
You can look it up on
You'll never you'll never get in there
But she but she did show it and it's on video and
Or if he seemed to be interested in how was it with the juicy, like she says, or with the dry.
No, but you can look at Krabby Joe and you can see what she looks like.
Krabby Joe.
Please, Joe Shipley.
Krabby Joe, it's another one. Oh, I all these random ones been coming up without her
acknowledgment
But with like her
So she doesn't know that she's being recorded
Like a 60 year old lady she looks 60 and her hair is
Really bad and you know, it's not it's not looking great for her. It's kind of like a tangled black wig
But I mean, it's like she's Persian big hair
Well, you can just look at Krabby Joe and then see what you think of that one, but there's another one
There's like three of those ones that I just came up, but it's Krabby and crap
But there's a couple joe or Krabby Joe
Crabby.
Like, like crab.
Crabbs.
Like crabs.
Does he have crabs?
No, it's a meme.
Okay.
It's a meme.
Okay, good.
But I don't want to recall that.
Like the nickname, like crabs.
Like it's like kind of like the Spongebob character,
Mr. Crabapple or Mr. Crabby.
Yeah, it's kind of a character from that.
Yes, sir.
I didn't watch that show, but I'm familiar with the characters Patrick starfish. I'm sponge ball. Well, this is an old fucking meme
This is like an old meme. It's an older than the biscuit meme
Oh, that was a 1995 so must be really really
Okay, it was a meme
Can you sing it a crab that was dancing, okay?
Well, this is getting ridiculous. They're talking about the little mermaid Sebastian in the kitchen scene
Okay
You didn't look up Krabi Joe channel. Just look up Krabi Joe channel
The cute
Let me have a look. Krabi Joe
Channel
Okay
Pictures of mice are coming a hamster is coming up. Oh
I don't know how many, but I thought it was very interesting.
Crabby Joe, okay.
Actually, there's a restaurant called Crabby Joe's.
It says Beatles.
Oh, Beatles, okay, let me look at that one.
And she, does he talk about Beatles?
I'll put the video right now.
Yeah, you can see it.
Okay.
You can see what she looks like differently.
Oh, is he near on this one?
I wanna see, let's see.
Crabby Joe and Beatles.
Krabby it's not all I see is a bunch of these the seafood restaurants called Krabby Joe's
If you streamer what I sort of beside Krabby Joe's streamer show. I've got the Krabby Joe channel
Yeah, that's what I saying put in Krabby Joe channel
Or I don't know. I don't know. I don't know what to put in it had popped up on my thing like oh, I see it
Or Augie and the cockroaches not so I have no clue. I have no clue. It came up once
It was all like Vita without more research on this. I'm seeing I think it's crazy cartoon and some like
Medicaid shampoo ads so that's like in fear
Before you go just reiterate
You were just joking about the pristine
Yeah, sir
Were you joking? You're just talking about the Alex stuff too just now, right?
What you're joking by the Alex stuff. She didn't like you know, whatever use those allegations
No, I was a hundred percent serious
Well
I'm sorry about that, but you're gonna find out really soon about Alex
I'm I've been telling you, you know, I love Alex. I have like a lover Alex. Uh-huh. Just cuz I
Hate to be I'm always the underdog, right? Oh
That was that was make music was Marty's nickname for me was underdog
Last one they expected
Um, hold on. Yeah, so, yeah, underdogs. So we're both underdogs, right?
So that, um,
to me, I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't want to be, I'm not, like I said, I'm not telling you what to do.
No, don't tell me what to do, but just tell me the truth. I want to hear the truth.
Well, she's a terrible person.
She's always been kind to me and, like, supporting me.
I know, but you're going to find out really soon that she's not nice.
You'd have to like listen listen let him find out on his own you don't have to warn him
You know what I don't need to be one. I don't that's what I'm saying
I don't want to say that to him, but I don't think she's gonna do anything bad to me
Oh, well, yeah, well, I didn't think she was gonna ever do anything bad to me
But she sat there and did her very bad weird things to my family and I don't even know
She personally did them to your family. Oh, yeah
And you know what the funny part is is that they just want to hurt her now, you know
In harms more harm's way than she because she doesn't know how big my you know, I have
over a hundred first cousins you know my second fucking cousin range that stupid fucking cunt
that bitch has just fucked around with me and my first fucking she pissed my mom when when somebody
i didn't want anybody finding out about this shit and let alone anybody in that realm where she's at
And now and now she's in even a better place for them to hurt her. Oh my gosh who?
Alexandra, yeah, we're gonna fuck her. No, you're not gonna do shit. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Just gonna run your mouth
Yes, you're gonna call the police on her and we're gonna get her fucking up for all the shit that
Whatever you do to her is gonna come back to you exactly exactly
Exactly. Exactly. Thank you so much. God, thank you so much.
If you do bad things to her, then bad things will happen to you.
God, thank you so much.
She's got so much bad shit. She's gonna get it. What's going on, man? She's gonna get a tin full. My dookie's not feeling good, huh?
She's got it coming from every direction.
You want me to heal him? I'll heal him right now. Put your hands on him and through you I will heal this dog. Sorry, sir.
We'll transfer that pain to someone else. You gotta wait till uh good boy. He's look at that good boy
Look at that beautiful boy. Oh, we've been checked out. Give him a kiss. Give him a give him a big kiss
Right there. There you go. There you go
He healed he's healed now. He's all better. Yeah, I don't think so, but maybe that's what we're feeding them
No, it's that's not what would happen because of this
How do you feel about this whole thing? You and Crystal Cool LD?
God, I fucking hate LD, dude.
Fuck you bitch you just keep name-dropping people acting like you're someone that you're not how many times you've been on the RV bitch
What friend what friend
Yeah, where where have you met her
I'm waiting, bitch.
I think she sounds great.
Go ahead, make a few more fucking bullshit.
Beautiful.
Here's pictures of me and Gucci hanging out.
Me and Manette, me and Captain Content, me and Chicken Andy.
Little pitchy.
And it made her so uncomfortable that she didn't want to say anything.
She stayed at my house for the fucking weekend.
And then she had a leave and then she had a phone call.
You abused her.
You fucking ate her out when she was completely passed out.
And she did not want to have sex with you.
And she said she possibly could have sex with you.
But she said, oh, if you remember, is you eating her out?
And then she would like ran away and that you ran away.
And then we hung out later on the RV.
I get used to the bandage ever,
and I hate your guys when they help you ride.
Who's this Gish?
You talking about Gish?
I hope you ride the hell.
No, I can't talk about Gish, she is.
Oh, good Gish, yeah.
You ate her out and she ran away?
You were that bad, huh?
No, no, she spent the dude she spent the weekend at my apartment
Like an AK-47 behind my bed
Situation people were just pissed that I was hanging out with Gucci's
Assaulted her and called it a joke. It wasn't the first time I'm sure
What? So it's so wait a second. I sexually assaulted her
Well, he knows where I live. She's been my fucking house. If she didn't know and she felt very
Uncomfortable, I know I know I hung out with her after that
All right, well, this is what happens when you watch too much people on the fucking internet
Yeah, and your teeth are falling on your face
Whatever bitch turn your fucking camera on
She just showed her feet about half an hour ago
I wasn't around you missed a good show
You want slippers though? Yeah
God this guy is a sick fuck
We can never all this bitch talks about it's sexual assault
Is that what happens in my friend my friend didn't know just enjoy crystal just enjoy
To take a serious she's never met Gucci's in her life
but this is her friend
her friend
i love my goopy
yeah when was the last time you talked to her
longer than you i mean
it probably has been longer than me
sooner than you asked
she hates you she fucking was like
disgusted by you
Oh, I'm glad you're she's still alive. Yeah, she's doing very great. She's actually really great
You don't even know where that fucking is
Yes, I do. I know exactly what she's doing. You're stupid if you don't. Yeah, I do
Well, then you are obviously, you know, you don't and you weren't your friend and you don't know shit about her
Stop acting like you do stupid shit
Yeah, okay
You're a faggot bitch. Oh my god, stop it
I need to stop it myself. Sorry guys. Sorry guys.
Don't worry, dude. We're going to the vet tomorrow. We'll get you checked out and get you some antibiotics. You'll be good
Get some for yourself, too
I'm really worried about him to be honest
Well, he's what is the lethargic
No, he's not lethargic. I just I was running my hand over him and I felt like a half inch wide mass on his on his armpits and
That's like typically where you're not typically that's where your lymph nodes are
I don't know about animals and should I had to look it up, but like that's your auxiliary like lymph nodes
So if you have swollen lymph nodes, it means your body is typically fighting an infection or you're fighting like cancer
So it's not big or anything. I'm hoping you just
Maybe got an infection he seems fine. It's probably your sister fucked them for her wedding day to art
Yeah, let's have check it out man, I wouldn't even I wouldn't even give you to my fucking dog
You probably give my dog some fucking shit you nasty bitch
well that's your sister she's the one that's a dogfucker we are
that's fine because you're you're the one that's a why we're not married
hey listen you guys you're the one that's such damaged fucking good you can't
find a fucking man did you name didn't sister after her
poor name thank her loves dude little Dylan little Dylan like a little
fucking dick Dylan likes that's her love name
Oh by the way, he used to videotape his sister at the beginning of her porn. Hey, let's talk about this
You know, she just got married crystal
Yeah, she married a dog
Uh, are you married?
Yes, you married have you ever been married not to a dog? You're not married currently are you?
Yeah, all right
So she just got married let her enjoy her marriage
It's crystal and I just got to run her fucking mouth about people cuz you got nothing else to talk about
Well, she did just marry a blue healer, I don't know
Who did she marry? Oh, do you like the guy is he cool?
He's a dog. He's all right. He's a fucking animal. He's you got money. He's a fucking
Blue he's not sure
Hopefully he's not a nice car. Oh a nice car
Hopefully he's got a nice house too. He's got he's got more than Chris Lee's got a job
Got way more than a job dude. I got my own house. I got my own car. I got a brand-new car
I got a old house, okay, whatever. Yeah
And I'm taking care of myself bitch
Wow, you're like 50 years old you should be taking care of yourself at this point
But my mom's got a sore sore arm right now. You fucking I'm taking care of myself. You're supposed to you're an adult
You dumb bitch. You're supposed to be able to take care of yourself, but you don't though
That's the point. I make I don't don't
You guys live off your parents fucking asshole
I don't even live in my parents house. What do you fucking do bitch? You're a fucking asshole parent of looking you you caught their house on fire
You stupid asshole. I'm not by the way your bitch and you guys think that we don't know
They all live in the same house together. They're so stupid. No, we don't
They have no money
like try to get these fucking streamers to fuck.
I love how she can just go from one topic to another,
just making her just walk away.
And you know what the fuck I mean?
She's so good at it.
She's like, oh, Alex talks to you about people's family.
You gotta admire it though, man,
how she can just do it.
It flows, it flows just naturally, it just comes out.
It's like diarrhea.
The truth, dude, I know way more than they even like.
She knows the truth.
She knows that, yeah.
Hey, she's got her fucking crystal meth bowl right there.
This Phillip motherfucker, Phillip Faggett,
Justin's fucking Phillip Faggett brother.
He fucking, his mother tried to fuck
the guy, the captain and another guy and then she was actually, do you know that woman that she goes by Miss Katz?
That's Justin's mom.
By the way, but she tries to fuck a lot of streamers.
And she got a lot of plastic surgery and she looks way better than
Justin Justin got fake tits and shit and she got like plastic surgery, but she still doesn't look good
Yeah, cuz we're so poor
because you guys your mother is a whore and your father prostituted them and
You know your dad prostituted your mother and that you were the fucking manager you're like your sister
Yeah, you guys are a fucking bunch of like disgusting humans. Yeah, it's a whole different life for you guys. I
'd rather be poor
Well, you are poor, so
I still have more than you
And imagine that I'm poor and I still have more money.
I have more money and you're down bad.
Yeah.
And your mother is down bad and your sister is down bad.
And so are the babies, okay?
The babies.
Yeah, your whole fucking family is down bad.
I just think it's so funny. You're like, oh Alex talks shit about families and you're here doing the exact same shit like 15 minutes later
Well, because you think it's okay for Alex to do it, right? Alex did it to me for fucking years
Yeah, so you think it's okay. No, I never said it was okay. Yeah, you think it's fine. You're a piece of shit
Yeah, I didn't think it's okay if Alex does that. I'm gonna do it too. Hey, what's the difference?
I've been around longer than Alex. So why isn't it okay if I did it?
It's not okay if anyone does it
Can retard
Fucking dyke
I'd rather I'm not a dyke. I just cannot date a female bitch boy
Yeah, well get back with good times. I heard his pussy smells too
How is that who you dated your old boyfriend, right?
You know
God him and and good times used to have like good competitions
Bacon biscuits out of her
You know good times L. D. He's staying out
On and then you say you hang out at good times. Oh, I did. I used to hang out at good times
That's how I know crystal is from a money. I got a good time. He looks like super gay, Gotti
Yeah
There's no good times over there
It's no good times. I only fucking talk to good times because I love good times as a friend
I've known good times for years. Yeah
And I care about good times
How many times have you met good times? You're such a good friend to them. How many times have you gone out and seen them?
Everyone knows that you're alive
I would never go meet good times
Zero, that's only because you're such a good friend
This is the truth
I would never meet good times
Good times than I would never meet
I've always told good times that
I've I've always told that to good times right from the very beginning. I I care about good times as a friend
But I would never meet him because he's creep is fun
But I care about him I think he's I
Feel bad for him. I don't want him, you know when he feels lonely
I you know, I want to be there for him sometimes
Chris of your friend Jim Nick is here. I love Jim Nick. What's up, Jim Nick?
Hey, oh
My gosh, Jimmy. Oh
I hope you're doing okay. I know you're doing good girl. You're always gonna you're gonna be on that ups and ups
I always tell her that you know like you guys
Ah, no, don't worry about it
Nobody's bullying me I
I, um, I worry about you and what I don't want you to think that I'm worrying about
because I don't want you to worry about me worrying about you.
Why am I bullying Crystal?
I do not worry about you.
She's been on here running her fucking mouth about everybody.
Who's mom you want to talk about
God I'm confused. Can you get me on track here?
Don't worry. You're gonna be on time. It's confusing me
You don't like this music. It's beautiful. It's confusing. It's Alex Meyers
Oh
Aaron is that you?
Well, how'd you sneak up here? I don't know
Is that really what Alex that was good. Yeah, that's fantastic
Like I didn't like that
What's going on?
You gotta say hi first.
I said hi.
Why'd you do it?
Say it again.
Hi.
Hi QQ.
What are you doing?
You look how beautiful this is.
Why are you doing this?
Just a second.
I don't know what's with this shit.
Just having a late night fucks festival here.
Hey.
Hey girl.
I don't know who you are.
You always know what I'm to text at three.
Listen to this song.
It's really cool.
What the f**k is that?
I'm just like the ears.
You want us to take off, Psyche?
No, you want you to stay and listen.
I listened, I love that one.
What are you doing?
My hair hurts.
You can't sleep?
No, I can't sleep.
Hi, LB.
You want me to fix it?
Yes, please fix it.
I put your finger in your mouth
and then put it in the ear that hurts.
No, I'm serious.
Okay.
All right, hang on, hang on.
Okay, ready like like almost like a wet willy, but stick it in your ear
Stick it in here now now hold your nose with your other hand
Mm-hmm, and then like blow but close your mouth and like blow like your pressure. I
Already did that
Do it again
You just want to hear me make that
All right, you never heard you then
It's gonna hurt anyway. Yeah, but I appreciate your help
Could be an inner ear infection
Got a hope not those hurts. Do you use q-tips?
Yeah, yeah, you're not supposed to
You're pushing that deeper into your ear
But it feels so good. Yeah, but you gotta flush that shit out with one of those little things that flushes off the wax
You probably have a lot of wax build up
Yeah, I guess they do the doctor's supposed to do it
Well, I'm probably gonna have to go and have them do it. I don't use that show use q-tips
You're not supposed to use q-tips
Yeah, they do
They'll do you okay
I'm just worried about my dog. I'm waiting for the doctor open
Wait, what what happened?
He's got like a swollen lymph node, so I'm hoping it's not cancer.
Oh, God.
So I'm waiting for that.
Yeah, I'm waiting for the vet to open at 8 a.m. So I can go take him to the vet.
That'd be good. Might be like a tick bite.
No, it's not a tick bite, but...
I'm just hoping it's like an infection or something, you know?
Yeah, that's scary.
Yeah.
Very, very early in.
So, yeah, I get your nervousness. I understand.
What is a clean ear?
Clean ear?
Clean ears. Yeah. It's a product.
It's like a corkscrew. It's like a little corkscrew. It goes into your ear and it pulls the stuff out.
What are you doing, sir? No.
Anyway, I'm not talking about cannabis.
Why not?
You might have TMJ.
No, TMJ is your job.
Listen, it has to do with your ear, smart guy.
It has to do with your jaw.
Yeah, but first, it makes your ears hurt.
Dude, if you had TMJ and how much pain you would be in,
she's in pain.
I'm in pain, yeah.
Not that much pain.
TMJ is like lock jaw.
Who just barked
My pup oh
Yeah, pop
Yes, you've seen my dog. He's in pretty much every picture
Scottish Terry
No, he's pit and
We doing
Malinois
So yeah, he's pit Malinois. That's cute
He's a good boy. Yes, he's a good boy.
Anyway, so besides us being worried for Duke,
and of course, Gotti being amazing as always.
No, I'm not Jamie.
Jesus, sweetie.
Do we sound alike Jamie come up
And I don't know this lady hi crystal Marie
She's not talking to you. Oh
Okay, I have that effect on people
What do people give you a complex
Don't get a complex from you. Don't get a YouTube complex
Except for Dave dump me for so many
Dave dumped you
I didn't know you guys were dating
The moves are engaged man they move quick calm on how what do you want me to say?
Tell me what you want me to say bae. I'll say it. It's wild
call out psyche. What? Call him out or call him. Call him to come back. I don't know.
We should come back. I never get to talk to him. Fiske. Who's Fiske? Fiske. No, he can't
be depressed. We'll help him. Come on. All right. Or nobody talk.
We're listening to you
We've been talking for hours
And you stop this as I come it's your turn. Oh, did you come?
It's about fucking time
That's why psyche said hey Fiske Fiske get back here
I love it when they write the name wrong.
Who pulled?
Wait, is that a pole?
Who pulled it? No.
Oh, no, no, no.
What do you want for Halloween this year?
Me?
Yeah.
A fairy.
A what? A fairy?
A fairy, yes.
Oh, that's what LD is going to be.
I'm actually going to be happy for Halloween.
Happy? You're going to be happy? Good luck.
Say good luck.
No, you have to be happy. It's my favorite holiday.
Mine too.
We'll have Halloween on Christmas.
Yeah, you're muted up here, Kristen Marie.
And then you went bye-bye.
Hello, Psyche. Come back. I voted.
You have to come back. I'm pretty sure my vote won.
What are your thoughts on that, Erin?
What's that?
The whole situation.
I'm foreign against it at times.
But sometimes you're more for than against yeah
But mostly against mostly for
Okay, I can see that oh
No, we're boring Jim Nick. Well, she can take her ass to fucking sleep. I'm so sorry. Oh
She's buddies with Crystal and she was the only interesting one. Okay. Yeah, we hear Jim Nick talk. She sounds like a 12 year old
Mm-mm
LD you ever here speak
Yeah, I've known Jim make for a long time. She has like a baby voice
We were gonna meet up when I was staying at the pluribals in Texas
What happened?
Oh, we never did I wasn't there for too long just a couple months
I think as soon as I left Texas she went up with deplorable
I think her and baser for went out there and met him. What a gang
And you wonder why all you people have fucking like fights and fucking want to kill each other I feel bad for her man
She's pretty sick right now
Jim Nick
She can't be too sick if she's here he'd be surprised got him
Yeah, this this place does wonders for people. I'm fully healed from me grinders
What else has been going on
Not too many healthy people around here. Oh
Ellie's get married. Um, what's your name? Aaron? Oh, yeah, I got engaged
Very nice. Who is she pop the question? Yeah
There she is. Wait, are you being serious? Yeah, dude. Yeah, pinkie face. Oh, that's amazing
Yeah, we're planning for next summer
Will you have the wedding?
and at a very
isolated island, you know
Go to India
They'll steal her. Don't go to India
No, congrats.
Yep, ladies.
Eldie's off the market.
Well, no, not where it's an open marriage.
Oh, well, he's back on the market then.
He's back on the market.
He has relived the market.
It's an open marriage.
She insisted that it be open.
Is her hair dyed, or is that?
Probably not for me.
Is her hair dyed that color?
No, it's not true. Yeah, we've been together a long time. Geez. You have dark hair
What a genius
Ever since me and my other fiance broke up
Who's that one that's the best looking one right there that's Alex. Oh wow, she's a smoke show
That's why she gets all the hate
Why she's a smoke show
We have it. I feel like that's racist. Who's that kid that you're with?
That's the same girl with pink hair, but like a couple years ago when we were in Vegas. You look like you're 12
We supposed to have the same thing he does look 12
There's her and Duke and our other greyhounds that we had to put down like a couple months ago. Oh the girl one. Yeah
Yeah, Penny
She was just old or she was sick
She had osteostarcoma and she fell down the stairs and broke her paw or her leg. I'm not sure and
She took her to the vet and they were either have to amputate and she would still die from the cancer
So there was really no reason to amputate. So
Just ended up putting her down
That gets you for a while. Actually, it still does. Yeah
I'm watching Alex right now. Alex is making a grilled cheese sandwich
He's cheating on her before the wedding. I don't think so Crystal Murray with onions and a seasoned grilled cheese sandwich. Sounds good
That sounds delicious
And why am I not getting any?
Make me one, please and thank you. Yeah, she should make us all one
I think so. Yeah. I think that sounds like a really good idea. He's just wanted a tip.
I'm sorry, you still look very, very young in those. I think in that picture I was like 28, 29, 30.
28, 29, 30. This one's recent, this one here? This one, no, this one was like right before we
Why'd you guys break up I cheated on her. Oh
She didn't like that. I didn't like that. Why'd you tell her I?
Didn't tell her she came home and found me on the couch with another girl asleep on an asshole dude
Do you really have a fucking asshole the patron? You know what the fuck? I didn't teach you anything. I was young man
I was young Jesus Christ younger
younger yeah
Yeah, it must have been fun when she walked in on that
It wasn't she started beating me up now she's gonna set your ass up now you're gonna come home and she's gonna be with three guys
probably three
You've already had an extra two. She doesn't look like the one guy type of girl
Are we talking about the pink hair lady?
I'm not the one girl. What do you want? What do you want from psyche? He's doing something
Is he doing something you want a reading I'll give you a fucking reading. What do you want?
Right now hold on let me get the cards
No, okay, you ready you got to go fuck yourself card how about that
I knew that was coming. Yeah, you knew it was coming. But you still wanted it. Oh
Yeah
The LD got kicked off for being too raw
And I was responding to chat he's eating something
I'm not even said I got up one. No, psyche is
Oh, maybe
Hey, he's eating on camera
All right, then I won't worry about it
Jim Nick HULD. I'm not even I'm not even sure that's what you do to her. I have a feeling that's the fake Jim Nick
There's a fake Jim Nick now, okay
Look at that boy
The boy
Can you feed him cheese can they cheese dude? I'm fine when we go to the vet. I'm gonna get him wherever the fuck you want
We're gonna get steaks
Get some steaks tonight Duke. Oh fuck your husband
Yeah, like I said this thing like under his armpit that I'm worried about so
Wait, let me see
On the other side actually
It looks like a, it is a swollen lymph node, I can tell just from looking at it. Hold on,
let me turn the camera around. Dude, come here.
Does it really, Jim Nick?
I'm going to have to try that.
Sour, air-head gummies.
All right, dude, turn it, turn, turn to the side, Duke.
Oh.
You see this red thing under like his armpit?
I do, yeah.
Yeah, it's a swollen lymph node.
Mmm, I mean he's either fighting an infection or he's fighting cancer. You know you should do get a hot needle go put the needle
No, it's a lymph node. Yeah, well you have to drain it dude. You're gonna drain that shit
Well, they're gonna drain it at the vet and they're gonna test it
Yeah, I'm not touching that shit cuz I can't test anything. You know what I heard if you if you drink that stuff
It you'll grow your hair back
Oh, I'm not
Sour candy something that makes you go coming over. I never knew that. I know that sour candies are really good for panic attacks
Or salt. Oh my god. What is she doing?
No, she's making this grilled cheese. She's putting time in it
Okay, picking it off the leaf like one of it one piece at a time
So she's a chef
Apparently she's not just cooking cheese. I don't know if you could put thyme on a grilled cheese
But you want to go cheese about that
You love it look at all the smooches he needs
I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't know what to do with it, I don't
Now you want to play it's time to play LD. Yes. Oh
Okay, I know you don't look too sick to me cold warning cold warning cold water relax relax
World premiere video
Let me get my belly dancing stuff on hang on
Shut up, I'm trying to listen.
you think i'm here to spread hate? is that what you want to hear? you want to hear more hatred?
are you sick fucks want to hear more hatred spread around this fucking place? you don't hear enough every
fucking day. you got ugly cunts like Hannah spreading her fucking bile everywhere she goes.
that's what you like, huh? you like hatred, you like fucking dirty hatred and lies.
I can give you fucking lies. You want to hear lies? I'll give you all the lies you want to hear.
But that's not me. I'm not that kind of person.
I only spread love and cheer wherever I go. That's why I'm God and you're not.
I'm a very positive person. I don't even talk about people.
It's mostly these assholes talking about others.
You ever notice that these people always say the same shit over and over again?
It's always something negative about somebody.
You don't hear any fucking positivity spread anywhere.
Go to a stream where it's 100% positive. You won't find one.
But you'll always find one that's 100% negative.
And like-minded people, they'll go there, they'll laugh about it, hee hee ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
with no life, spread her bullshit.
That's very positive Hannah, very positive person.
And you know why people like you Hannah? Because they just like you.
Lonely, ugly cunts.
Men and women.
No life. Oh yeah, you have the receipts, I'm sure you do.
Maybe you won't be able to find him though in that fucking horde that you call a fucking room
Why don't you take five minutes and clean your fucking house you dirty bitch
You know she sleeps with toilet paper on the bed
Why is that Hannah? Why do you sleep with toilet paper on the bed?
You fucking just lose your bowels while you sleep
You just fucking let it flow, huh? Right there on the bed.
Nasty bitch.
Clean your fucking sheets, bitch.
I'm a Gemini, man.
The best.
Two that make one.
Yes, like he's gone for the day. I'll be taking over for the next six hours
So get used to it
Welcome once more to another live stream of Cooking with Kat.
I am your hostess, Alison Vermeers.
And remember, if you'd like to learn more about me,
you got to do a pop on over to alisonvermeerslive.com
or you can visit cookingwithkat.com.
I'm just going to make myself, I guess, an early dinner and plate lunch today.
some stuffed peppers designed for my cup of tea.
But yeah, I guess tonight's meal is going
to have a little bit of a Latin flair to it,
a little bit of a Tex-Mex kind of feel,
because that is where I'm designing right now.
All right.
A lot of peppers.
It looks kind of like a chili pepper.
And by no means am I a cooking culinary expert yet. This is just me having fun with you. That's it.
Olive oil we're going to implement. And let me tell you lady something, okay. Please,
if your diet allows you to, you know, of course, could float with your dog or whatnot.
please implement olive oil into your diet. It makes all the difference in the world.
I have been feeling really energetic and my joints naturally as I get older. I've been
I've just been feeling a lot more energetic,
more about my body has felt looser,
my skin has been really glowy lately.
And I was thinking, I'm like,
what if I'm gonna do it different?
And I'm like, okay, I can home cook it more,
which I'm sure makes a difference
when I'm getting better nutrition
from, you know, opposed to eating out.
And I was like, okay, what have I really been eating?
I have been eating a lot of garlic, definitely.
I'm gonna eat the one who's the best, I'm just gonna eat the one who's the best
I don't need some with hands, the boys tryna chop me up
Talk about cryptocurrencies, how do they shut you up
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah
Standing there feeling like ABC's, somebody making stuff
Me, I'm so excited, if they love me, I'd cover it
If you're standing next to me, better understand
Bones at sea, milkshake with my fries
Protective of my energy, drink you with my vibes
What a girl wants, what a girl needs
Want somebody to talk to me so sweet
Thank you so much for watching this video, see you in the next one!
What am I?
I'm hot too, I'm Pilates
Videos from me and I don't plan on making copies
Did I hurt your feelings, baby?
Boy, go tell your mommy
Damn
baby watch me look inside my movement eyes you might die if you get my seven
calling pink moonlight body tight side to side but i'm moving got you calling
bend your back oh i'm freaky damn make it look easy double the weight that you
Baby, watch me
Sexy silhouette, snicking round in the rain
But I'll make you sick, so obsessed for a good time
Oh, oh, oh, oh, I'll make you want me
Oh, oh, oh, oh, baby, watch me
Five, ten, hundred, one
Girls want cash, girls want to have funds
Getting drunk off your attention
Stack so long it, make a girl run
That stash it that I love
Throat so fast, you gotta paper cut
But out the club, now it's just us
Straight from the bottle, like uh, uh, uh
Such as you, let's make it round in the rim
But gotta make you sick, so obsessed for a good time
Ay-oh, ay-oh, ay-oh
I'll make you want me
Baby, watch me
Beautiful vixen by nobody else knows. She's got an addiction to the powder in her nose.
The touch from her lips will leave you turned to stone. You better all feel known.
She's too hard to listen, always stuck in the clouds. Pain in her picture, better subside down.
I bet that you wish that you'll never kiss, but it's too late now.
Don't get too lost in her eyes. All she wants...
This is a bite of your hide
I don't wanna know where to hide
There's a devil in my room and I don't mind
So suck it, don't touch it
Cause he might just lose
She'll never listen, cause she never cared
Sings like a siren, but you should be scared
Cause when you leave, she doesn't act the same
She's under the sheets, pours and drips on her veins
And you drink it up
And just lose your life
Careful for the poison up a sleeve
Touch you in the morning and haunt you in your dreams
So suckin', babe, love it
But they never leave in the right
Talk sick, lullaby
Kiss your comfort, so goodbye
Turn you to stone with the look in her eye
But you're never all the same
She used you to escape her mind
Abuse you, cause that's what she likes
She's torturely best, she's your favorite mess
She hurts me all the time
I don't wanna run away to hide
There's a devil in my room and I don't mind
So suck it, don't touch it
Cause you might just lose your life
Careful for the poison up his sleeve
Touch you in the morning and haunt you in your dreams
It fosters deeper and attaches itself to me in ways that seem almost impossible to break.
It's as if I need the pain to keep me whole.
me down I cannot surprise I know your kind the truth is no chains no roads don't
need them I'm not going home can't be alone you hurt me and I'll pull you close I can't
tell you why let you kill me with a smile I don't want to lose it wish I could
Can you see inside my mind?
I'm lost, I learn from pain, I grow the light within the shadow
MEDEVAL
That switch side
Love, not me
I'm shadow band again
Pop, pop, pop, pop
Bro mute your mic
Then boom
Drop a bass line dirtier than the chat
is crashing out, smashing routers like vows.
Canada dries, lick and watch catalog somehow.
Randall's ranting bout A.I. Toons,
while his playlist's all cartoons.
Mason's pacing, red-eyed rage,
threatening people from an undisclosed stage.
Natalie Benz's back, pushed behind head.
Mod's praying, Lord, not again.
From the bone, brags he just dropped a cosmic load
Alex and his mic, nuclear loud
Beat the storms and turn it down, you clown
Strony bombs, the stream with skin, chat explodes
Mods dive in, he man in time, rogue and free
Burning bridges, living HD
Authors, they're just smiling sweet
Y'all need Jesus, or at least some sleep
And it's all so true
Ghost is connected
Canada drive timed out
Randall's still typing
Wait, Debita just banned me
Laughter static at me
I'll
Endstream
They whisper in the livestream static
Who's that voice, smooth and ready?
Camera's hung, the cosmos bends
Father's psyche's back again
Crown of truth, robe of flame
Calling out patrols by name
Stay there, the soul, every panel's a cosmic scroll
Lenors at his feet like a priest, his feet line
Tricks and lola guard the shrine, he speaks in riddles
Laughs at sin, Rudy and Marbles just stare at him
He breaks your doubt with cosmic ease
Yeah, he's seen the lies, the feuds, the fall
He built a verse to outshine them all
He don't flinch when the weirdos call
He just grins, says, welcome y'all
Wisdom wrapped in nemen madness
Love and logic, joy and sadness
He turned your chaos into art
He'll roast your soul and read your heart
Light the candle, hear the perch
There's one show he spins the stars and makes them glow
Father Psych, Keeper of Night
Who does he think he is?
But I got glitter nails and a crystal sphere Doug D talking like it's 1952
Racist rants. Yeah, I banned you too back, but every troll that clicks my stream just feeds the fire in this mystic queen
Your trauma dunk don't trigger much, yeah
Keep watchin', keep that frown
Cause trolls make the world go round, down
JT and Reigns devilishly hot
If Lucifer had a twitch, they'd co-host the spot
Cute little demons with chaos in their eyes
But even they know not to cross these
important like he's trying to destroy but guess what psyche don't fold you're just
every single one of you.
Stop, together, panel verse, we're going to the top
Christine, you're the healer, the heart so wide
You check on the broken, you stand with pride
Crystal, you're chaos, and I say that with love
You're a glitter bomb falling from the skies above
Summer, oh sultry, you turn up the flame
Just to show it's commu-
This is your brain.
Um
These glasses don't help
Look a little bit better
Really crazy or no
Trying to go for like the less crazy look
Anyway, I played some stuff like that I did and I played some things that I like and some things that are inspired by some things that I like.
And so I was like surprised to see that there was like a lot of people here like cool for me it's like you know
Like, sometimes I'll start a show, if I start a show with a music video and people come in,
like, nobody, nobody, like, no one will come.
They'll just leave immediately.
But, I think it's just like, if I hate watchers, I think,
if I do have a lot of hate watchers, I probably have like,
20 people here that never comment or anything.
I'm just sitting here, and then I say, I figure out who one of them was,
because I say, go to Sandman's today,
and I want to give away all my secrets, how I do things,
but I say, go to Sandman's, and then I went, like, over there.
And I was like, I went to see who's going to say,
Pete, I just texted you.
And I sent somebody to it, and I was like, oh, I'm good.
OK, anyway, so there's people that are here all the time,
basically.
I mean, I'm not saying her spice, but I have spice, too.
But I'm going to say, again, not to give away too much
information, but it's like, and I'm going to say, they're not
even like, oh, they're just saying, volunteer, I mean,
they volunteer, you know, just to like, yeah.
I'm not sending people out or anything.
I'm just, I hear about Jake.
I'm not a Jake.
And that's like the one thing I'm just thankful for
is that as long as you have one person
willing to tell you the truth,
because nobody's gonna tell you the truth
hardly anybody, if you have one person
that you can actually listen to
because they can deliver it the right way,
you're the other person.
You'll never figure out who it is.
But it's okay.
Because everyone should have that person. I hope you guys have a person that at least will
tell you everything that they know. In order to help you instead of like trying to, that's
like the Charlie the chocolate factory person, right? Who like, it's been tempted by something.
or ethics or something like that, or at least I won't be the one to do it, like I'll just
be out of that little hive, but do what you want to do. Okay, let me see, how's the chat doing?
Does anyone want to come up? I can put up the link. You voted yes? Did someone vote yes?
Um, go spot me in mansion
You bought the piano
The hardware
Hello
I'm gonna say hello. Hello
My little baby
baby
no babe
okay sit down sit down
i was purring i guess how are you nice thanks for coming
hi guys yep i finally finished i mean i think i played i was like i mean i said i have like a
lot more a lot more to play but i was like yeah i played played it though i was like this is
Thank you, and I really like I don't know. I like you guys too. I think and that's why I never like complain about like really
Anything about the people like in the community like that's like people that are really like hate me. It's like it's like it's just
You know, there's just like a lot of people that just like you know
leader anything people tell them and so and like a lot of people trying to like interfere with relationships and like
Cause more chaos and drama and stuff. Oh, no, are you just comfortable? She's comfortable
No, you look weird. Come on. You look don't look that month or she's live guys. She's alive
You want to chat a spoken what Jenny then you got that you got the pull rigged
But you know what the pull rig means is that imagine me and Jenny? I mean you let me to take over your show
I mean, how dumb can you be? I mean I had to learn far away because I literally take over my show one point
But you know what Jenny?
You shouldn't know you should've known better. I thought you were like oh
I should disappear
Can someone make Janney disappear from my chat, please?
Unlike people that voted the opposite the way they're not supposed to go in the pool
It's okay. You can be in the chat. I don't care early. Hey, but the nor the nor you're live, right the nor please
I don't I can't I can't have people saying I did the nor
Please wake up wake up. You're just comfortable. She just relaxes my arms. You thought I love beta
Yeah, you don't understand what a complicated relationship means Danny
I do love beta, but it's like I do I in love with her. No, do I think she's in love with me? No, I
Just want to be friends is why they're getting so like complicated beyond. I just want to be friends like that's like with everybody
I don't want to be eating beyond friends with anybody, especially and I don't think I would get anybody in that from the panel verse because it's like there's too many like
You know, kind of weird, I'm just kidding.
But it's just doing it like, know each other
and it's like everything would just be a big gossip.
You know, what's someone that's like,
I don't care if you're on the computer
and like doing that bullshit,
but it's like, you know, come to bed.
When I say you come to bed and like, you know,
I'm your priority, right?
It's like, instead of like,
oh, let's go see what she's saying.
Let's go, let's go blackmail these people.
I mean, it's like, what kind of bullshit is going on?
You know, I don't know if I'm saying it right.
I don't know.
But, you know, it's just like,
I don't know it's like in this community too. It's like I mean I came from the black sector
I mean it's like if you imagine like I'm just like gay white guy from the black sector in an online
Relationship with a crypt from Texas, you know, and I just say everyone was going kind of wild and I just kind of like
Took that as like oh, it's funny, you know, and then so they hit on the next street guys
And it was funny there, but then it's like everyone here is a
Like some kind of like the black people are I have a better sense human white people
I just have to say I'm sorry. I don't want to be racist, but they just do
I'm sorry
You know the band it's fine. He's fine
I mean Jenny's just a miserable person because Jenny has nothing to do but spread lies about me and Benny and like fine
They see they look for something where there's nothing right?
But Jenny at least has you know Jenny the clip show and I don't want to be clipped in the other way
So please don't fan him
Do you want to play some fish taco song or something?
I thought I had the things covered with making fun of myself, but no, no, people can do it better than I can.
But you know what, don't look for that song either.
It's very offensive. I wasn't asking, I was trying to get data so I could go get the fish tacos at the pier.
I had money for the fish tacos. It's always me making money for fish tacos.
It's just such a misinterested story. You guys only need the true lore.
But, uh, yeah, I can't go through it all, so it might take hours.
Uh-oh.
Go clean my floor.
My floor is so clean.
Oh, you're talking to me?
My floor is clean.
I can show you my, my place is actually as clean as it's ever been, like, for a long time.
And I did used to, like, not be such a clean person, I would say.
I was just, like...
It's more of a hoarding thing where I had a much smaller place and I had a lot more
stuff.
So now I'm in a good state where I just have enough stuff.
I have enough stuff where I have stuff to show you guys for the next ten years comfortably.
I go very slowly with what I bring out.
That's why I stick with a deck of cards for months, right?
I'm going very slowly, revealing all this up I have, I really have a lot of cool stuff, which is my vision.
I just brought out a little fraction of what I have, but it's hard to know what to share sometimes
because you share with people and all of a sudden you have a bunch of Scientologists
just picking you outside your house and stuff.
stocking part of thing. I don't like... I'm saying too much already.
Do not go to your personality test. Do not get on a mailing list. Do not read
Dianetics. Do not pass GO. Elrond Hover by the way was a ginger. Okay, and so we're
gonna like take a religion down to buy a ginger. I mean, we know they have no
Why are we gonna follow that revolution? You're the guys. Uh-oh, I can't
Oh being Patriot vibes. Oh shit. Why am I being compared to the vegan Patriot my male vegan Patriot?
Maybe she's my twin flame, but that's what I've heard about that
She's cooking because I look at me being Patriot. That's cooking. I think I think
It's like putting like a piece of toast bread in the toaster. I mean, that's kind of easy
I'm talking about you have to like, you know, it's cooking is like, you know,
satein and giving them juices and like scraping up the burnt bits and like
creating a sauce out of that and then, right, not just like throwing a piece of
toast, a bread and a toaster. Am I good and no, especially now that you're here. I
don't like you, random guy. Well, look at random guy, same man's here,
calling me unworthy. No, I'm just kidding. I did not endorse that. Am I good? No, I'm not good.
Yeah, we're talking about cooking. We're talking about panel where it's cooking right or like where it's like I'm cooking papas
Like it's like I thought I meant they were cooking potatoes, but actually it's like salmon like hitting on a guy
I'm just kidding Sam. It's a joke
joke
Yeah
anyway
Began to move into the psyche department
Well a guy I mean, well, I don't know if I'm gonna move her in here
But she, hold on guys, she got paid over $100 for sitting on that cake, right?
It smells like it makes them burn in my kitchen or something.
She has to put like a little blanket over the cat bed.
I've seen her, but listen, her dog
is going to be like wearing outfits, okay?
My cats are going to want clothes of their own.
It's going to be very expensive.
She has to bring some cat outfits.
I mean,
does she have any cat outfits?
Does she have a cat?
Yeah, anyways, let's not um
Imagine if I imagine if vegan page, we're not had a kid that was a kid was like can somebody please make that today
I don't I don't I don't know but she's vegan without ever where she real vegan or is that just say one of the
She's like one of the fake vegans that just has that for her name
Isn't it like poo? I have a backyard. I have it. I'm in chairs in the backyard
I don't want to move in with anybody.
It's nice and tidy this morning.
It's a thicket.
Are you swearing?
I think there's a U.
Not a thicket.
Not a U.
Well, it was the in-patriot that lady that was like delivering door-gash and she had like a little dog and pooped in the door-gash
And then she like delivered it and then she like hit a pedestrian on the way back home
That's not something I would do
Play us a song mr. Pianoman
Then you can make it happen. Yeah, okay. I need airfare. I need like actually put us in a hotel
I don't want to stay at her house. I don't know. We'll be sleeping in a dog bed seriously
And here they should be doing the same thing I kept it so that we have to be concave
Put us in a nice hotel and they get make it happen. Maybe some magic will happen, right? Who knows
You know champagne and piquilla, let's do it
Sammy doesn't have a litter box like he don't let him tell you you don't you showed your first
I know he did not show it and I just show mine. Yep
I did show mine and you know, I didn't say, you know, it was it was a gift because I really don't need it
And the cats line use it because like I said my cats are body trained people just don't listen
They want to believe like the worst thing that was I actually literally said oh his walls are covered in shit
It was actually like the camera like went on the table
There was like some ash and like the back on the table that turned into like it was like my carpet was full of shit
And then it's like a turn it's like if you say anything or just tell anything
People will just say the stupidest thing,
then it's like, then you can't really correct it.
All of a sudden it turns into, you're using your animals,
and then, thankfully, I know the police are around here,
and my mom, we have a person named Asis,
and they know all about what's going on.
So I've never had a problem with any kind of police
department or anything, but yeah,
I'm just very lucky.
Actually, I was like, luckily I had a family
that was in this police department, so I got it.
Like he's so um
Then anyway, I think just maybe there's any problems like new reports, but
Like I'd like to buy your pee pads for the dog. Okay
Yeah, I mean is that does he have an animal? I don't know if he has cats
So he definitely needs a litter box like he's in New York
So obviously isn't like in a little like apartment in New York, right? So you can't have like
Like you can't not have a litter box, right? I have a cat door and it's like I can show you the cat door
This is what I was like really showing you did that night where she's like I was like on the verge of s u i c i d
No, I was all I do with like two pictures. I took a picture of like a little house
I have outside for the cat is a cat house my neighbor built a huge mason and he like built its perfect little house and then I
Have a cat door that goes outside the cats can come in and out as they please
That's why I sent pictures of and then she turned it to like I was like, you know, you know on my left
And then the worst thing that she said she said just do it. Just do it. It's like, what is this banky bitch?
It's like, you know, you don't say just do it to people
It's if you think that they're actually doing that then I wasn't but it's like, why would you say that? I mean, that's so rude
It's like that's the guy goes along with the Aaron Carter stuff
That's why it's like I go hmm
I go to the air car and not trying to like accuse her or anything or in continuing anything
I'm saying there is a mindset of like oh
People that are depressed should just unalive themselves or people that are like, you know, or like they're there's a reason they should like
And that's something like that girl that taught the guy how to do it
She's the oh sit in your truck and put the hose in the window and stuff and then they turn it off
And then she likes I don't have any texts until he passed away. Yeah, and she was she got like one year or whatever
But I think that that was a
mindset of certain people like
I don't know if they think it's like social Darwinism or like some kind of like or just like trolling people to death
You know, that's what I see like happened there and I asked Jim Nick and Jim Nick supposed to be the sweet girl
and I was like Jim Nick
Um, why were people trolling erin carter or like, why were you doing? I mean, what's why were people involved?
And she's like, well, he was a drug addict and he was doing drugs every day
And that was like the mindset of like like what what do you mean?
Okay, how do you wear a drug so he deserves to be gangstocked and and you know, basically kill
I mean, it's like I don't know what happened. He's in a green bathtub
But people just bring him over like huffing things or I don't know. It's just
He is not trolled if he was a junkie, okay, well
I'm from I know he was huffing huffing is usually not like lethal like I mean if they can be but it's kind of rare
He would also like I'm saying there's the people around you make a big difference as to like what you do
He was a bath bomb
If it's made of bath salts or something like that like some shirm bath. I don't know bath bomb
I really was a bath bomb. It was like it doesn't turn into the color of nuclear waste
It was like her his bath tub was literally green like if you look at it, you can search Aaron Carter's bathtub
They said did he get it? Yeah, no, maybe you know and how hard is it to say hey?
Go give this guy some like free drugs, but you know, they're poison, right?
It's like how hard is it for a millionaire to do that to somebody?
If you think about it, if you just think about it, like if somebody is, especially if they're sociopathic, psychopathic,
I'm just like entitled to see if they can then do that to people, right? How hard is that?
Like...
Do it. Oh, here. Here's like, you know, a couple gift cards. Go harass this person, you know, or go pretend he's this person's friend and then like...
We can pull the rug out from under them and blow up all of my questions
We'd be answered if you just watch a couple of the documentaries. Okay, I'll watch it
Where does be it and trolls you to attack Aaron Carter here, but I don't think about it though
Well, it's like that's what's weird because it's like
Is
Be a trolling me think you guys see it's like if she was saying like when I was talking to you there day
She's crying. Hey, rando. Thanks for the laugh. It's a little odd stuff. Yeah, you're welcome. But yeah
Vita was like, oh, you know, she was crying and stuff like that.
And then she's like, well, then she's like, did you see, like,
and I'm sorry to like play you like a song, but I just said,
she's like, did you see that this, you know, that this poem,
she's like, that was about you.
And I was like, okay, I looked at the poem and it was like,
it's this poem and it's very like hallmark reading cards.
It's short, only a minute long.
So we're thankful though,
because it's like hallmark reading cards like,
I love you but it's not gonna work out kind of thing and it's like so it kind of sounded like it could be for me
but then it's like I was like well it sounds like it's too like kind of lovey-dovey to be like
you know really about me but and then she's like and I told her and she's like oh that wasn't about
you that was about um her ex-boyfriend or something this is this is the poem
All right.
And cherish every moment
I love you every day
So that was the poem, I put it to music.
Okay, it didn't come, but it's kind of a little bit over the top
and then she's like, then she's like, why do you think I'm in love with you?
I was like, well I don't, but she did when I met her, she did like, think I was kind
of cute when I met her, but I don't know if she was like, you know, not being
serious or something, but she said like
Oh, you're cute, we'll like hang out one day, we'll just cuddle, like I'll be like, okay,
I'll be fine, like just to cuddle, but not in an attraction or like a sexual way, I
got, there's, and it's like, and then it's like, you know, of course I've never even
met, you know, but you're a boy at home, it's been over, like a year now, you know, we're
here.
So you can go here feeling about a lot of people who love me, and people try to not
Not so much. Yeah. Well, that's why I kind of wanted to come to the community too because I'm like, well
I could do better. I could do like better here like with people, you know, I could do like
More good for people I could like help more people and a thing because I'm like kind of like
The certain kind of sense of humor for their kind of sensibility
That I can relate to some for a thing. I also feel okay. You see, I don't think you too trolls or
Who oh, yeah, okay. Yeah, but I'm saying like
They're not YouTube trolls like they're on discord and they're on like other like it was like a whole universe
And okay, you know what they call his donators the disabled queues. Hey, what's up?
Trishalicious Trishalicious might know about this like or more about this
I was just I was just saying like Jim dick had said that
You know, I was like, well, why was Aaron Carter being like harass or troll or whatever?
She's like, well, because he, you know, he did drugs every day.
And it was very like blog day, as she said it, like, I was like, well, how does that have
to do with like, deserving to be bullied or I just don't understand.
So, you know, but it was sad, I saw him and Dr. Phil when they tried to do an intervention
I thought he was a I thought he was a cool guy. I always liked him
but he kind of like, his brother was like Nick Carter, or his Nick Carter, right?
Yeah, I thought he was the most looking guy that's actually cool.
You feel any smell in me?
Yeah, I don't know what's wrong with Jim Nick. Like Jim Nick was supposed to here earlier too, and I don't know if it was a fake Jim Nick, but
Then I'm hearing other stories like I just don't like hearing something about like
Baking cancer or stuff like if people accuse me of like asking for money for fish chocolate
Well, I heard a story with and I don't want to accuse it. It's like here's a story about like
She'd beg for $10 so she could go to the hospital
And then she was seen buying alcohol like a bottle of alcohol liquor store
I don't know that just seems like it's like you I mean it's there
Whatever you're buying didn't tell what you're really gonna buy or like, you know, especially don't pick cancer because
It might probably die of cancer and there's not plenty of people, it seems like a lot
of people or some people have done that and so it seems like the Munchausen or Munchausen
disorder.
Yeah, I mean women are jealous of Tricia but have you seen Tricia in a bikini with her
So it's straight. Okay. No, no, no. Yeah, can you please a monster? There's like slander stuff or you know, just take it out
Yeah, well, I see black RG was that something like it's like didn't she wasn't she like
And she's saying like she's like about and then she said something about her tumors or her the cancer which she's like
Oh, it went into remission
Like if she's not under treatment and it's like it just seems like it's like
Because it sounded to me like what I was told right I think by her was that it was like spreading and I say I know that once
It's bad that the spreading part. I'm sorry if you want to hear this stuff. Okay. I'm sorry once you're the spreading part of it
Yeah, just blocking anybody that bother or you just blocking yourself or blocking to the chat
But yeah, but once the cancer spreading it's not going to go malignant
You know, it's like it just doesn't seem like it makes sense what she was saying
Or how I don't know. Yeah, it was a heel and stuff
So I don't know and it's like I just don't like the idea of it
And it's like right and then she did blackface too. What is that about?
The warlock dude can make her do it
He make her do it the first time and the court is car like
Carl okay, silver fox. He is like, you know, he's not an attractive man, right?
Kind of like reminded me of like some kind of like Miami
like interior decorator or something, okay?
And so, Opanda, maybe we gotta see the Orlando Brown stuff.
But anyway, so, yeah, he just seemed like it was like,
you know, he's a nice, kind of lit, nice looking guy.
He kind of like.
You just tell you but he's when he's on my show. He was a dick to me. Okay, so how do you treat me?
I will like remember I remember he was a dick and I didn't like really like him on the panel
Then it was like he was like, oh he just saw him beat it on he just got so excited
He was like almost like stalking me and what beat had told me is like she's like well
He's though. He's a warlock. He practices black magic
He had me in like you know some kind of mind control and then
He put a curse on me in that and the curse worked and my life has been
like a mess ever since.
That's what she told me, okay?
I don't know, Trish, you can just,
you know, just block them, you know,
or block them, you can hide them if you want.
Yeah, and so.
And then so then today in Alex's chat,
like I was in there, I was like,
I think he has some feelings for Bita as I know.
And then he's in there and he's like,
like you don't know anything about me boy
or something like that.
Or he's like, I don't have feelings for a boy.
And I was like, I'm not your boy, old man, whatever.
And Alex was like, Saki, you need to calm down.
You need to chill out.
Like, you know, she's like, leave him alone.
I was like, okay, I was like, now I got it went too far.
But it's like,
Hold on, who are you talking to?
Ray?
Who are you talking to about what?
Oh, yeah, so they just joined it.
Hopefully they're not involved. I've been replaced by the white fox.
What's- well, I mean, please, replaced, I mean, it's like, you know, you can never replace me first of all, you know, but second of all,
If people replace me with whatever, it's like beta.
But I replaced by Katie, Sweet Pea, and Bronzeberg.
Have fun.
It sounds like hell in a handbasket hanging out
with those three all the time, right?
I'd rather hang out with me personally if I was here.
But okay, whatever.
Oh, there's Samman.
The real Samman?
Okay, it was a joke, okay?
I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're saying, I don't know what you're
I can't, let's see, wait a sec.
You know, can you all just kiss or suck or make up
whatever you prefer, because society,
I don't think, are you talking about me or someone else?
Because I don't think Vita wants to make up,
because I try, yeah.
I'm just gonna make sure it's the real Sam and
I don't want to be duped again.
I got one today by some other dude.
Hello.
Who's me, Nicko?
Don't say the N word, okay, how are you?
He's calling me Trisha Lyon
Trisha Lyon, Eric Carter didn't like her ass.
Trisha's not lying. I'm sure she's not lying. She's a very honest.
How do you know Trisha's not lying? You wasn't the one that Eric Carter was around?
What'd she say about Eric Carter?
I think that you don't do that.
Eric Carter didn't like her ass. So shut the fuck up then.
It's like if you don't know what I'm talking about.
Well, I saw a video where it's like...
Hey, you saw a video. You saw a video of this and saw a video of this.
You don't know nothing
That's why I'm looking for information, but I'm saying I'm trying to dig up information
I'm saying I was to what I was told by Jim Nick was kind of like gross to me
And I'm just wondering what is this thing about people in like wanting to reach them like I don't know what it is
Why are you screaming? Why are you screaming?
What you're acting like I'm kind of like weirdo or something on my own show you're weirdo
Hello?
Hello, why is Sam and on here lying about me and acting like he knows what the fuck
Like he's spouting
You should do the word sit out that he passed away he didn't fuck with you really he didn't
Right, Trisha, please.
That way I have text messages from him telling me how much he wants to say inside.
Please, he was a nobody to him.
You're a fucking reimagined you had you had your minor daughter cursing at Aaron Carter after he died
You don't know what you're talking about
Why would you let why would you tell your kids to curse you?
the dead out like that.
You know, just clips around.
That's a lie, that never happened.
So what happened?
You're a fucking idiot.
First of all, when, how stupid can you fucking be?
You are so fucking retarded.
Do you not realize what age my fucking daughter was
in that video?
Like you are too fucking dumb to function saman you are really so he wasn't there yet or he wasn't there yet
That's why nobody liked me cuz I'm a fucking weirdo creep that fucking stands up for a fucking PDF all the time
I could do because I'm a bad owner and I'm a bad mom
How many dogs that died in your and your and your fucking custody how many dead animals is in your bag on
Come fucking find out
You want to join them?
Okay, whoa, you can put me in the backyard. I might if I can I don't take me long time to dig a big enough hole for your fat fucking ass
I'm just saying a lot of you people don't forget you you had your daughter cursing at grown-ass people
Like fucking five fucking years ago you stupid fuck okay, so it did happen
It did happen fucking killed your dog. So whoa. I didn't kill my dog. You can
How I neglected my dog
Me how come your dog didn't get to live a long doggy life salmon you tell
Trisha he lived a long life Trisha
He was a rescue to he was a rescue dog more than I had that dog more than 10 years not more than a
Really? I had that dog more than 10 years more than 10 years
Wow
And he was arrested that's what you say now. I've been I've been said that I had a morning
So you know what I've been hearing who who heard from who clumsy dank our row and Alex
Everybody yeah, the same hold on the same Alex that talked about your daughter and took big cheese and talked about your daughter
Now y'all got kissing Alex ass after she
I don't credit you as a bad mom. She's had bad mom. Now y'all won't kiss her ass. This shit is hilarious
That I'm not kissing your fucking ass
I never want you to kiss my ass
Trisha, I never Trisha one thing about me Trisha
You can say I went Trisha one thing one thing you can say about me. I never talking at your kid
Alex did and now you cool with her yikes
Yikes, first of all, I don't fucking know that
Yikes yikes yikes yikes
Yikes, I never
and talking to people you don't know shit about.
Yikes, yikes, I'm Sam and the fuck it.
I stick up for a pedophile every fucking day.
Yikes, yikes, I stick up for a pedophile,
groomer in fucking dance.
Oh, yikes, I'm always pedo.
Yikes, yikes, yikes, yikes, yikes, yikes, yikes, yikes.
I stick up for somebody that actually groomed
a fucking minor.
To the end had a move in let me get this concept. I got the concept right here
I'm doofy I'm the goofy doofy Sam
Yeah, you you went back to Alex. I think she exposed you remember Trisha Thursday
Remember Trisha's Thursdays remember Trisha Thursday. Oh, don't forget big T how big T talked about your daughter, too
Yeah, I love you baby. I love you baby. I never talked about your family baby. I'm not dumb. I'm not dumb
Trisha, I never told you about your family baby. Stop it
Trisha, oh, I'm not using nothing. I'm this is
Happen stupid
Wow, I just can't believe the nerve of him
He's so fucking and he had the nerve to call you fucking names on your own panel
And he's fucking the stupid fucking idiot
Yeah, really
I just don't know why he comes out here talking about trying to talk about fucking Aaron Carter and the Carter verse shit
That he was not he was not even around until like fucking years after Aaron passed away
So what the fuck is he why is he talking like he fucking knows anything? What an idiot?
And I mean I don't mean to bring it up really except like I remember like watching a lot like during the time of like
You know, I kept it's kind of keeping up with it
And then I have a friend that like knew him too who is like also into like being hailing stuff like huffing stuff
And so I don't know yeah, and so like she's in prison right now for like the next 20 years
Yeah, she would hang out with him and stuff and so I like knew about people that were around him and so and then I say
Sometimes when I just like hear information it's like it's just weird how like it just like it syncs with other stuff
I've heard and stuff
So I was just so then I like that woman crystal Anne or whatever. I think she I mean she's still around
I mean she I've seen her be this chat and stuff. I think so. I mean I don't know
It's like I think she's around like she's a terrible person too
Oh my goodness.
Well, Meena is like, you know, just being so weird with me,
like she was saying, oh, like, you know,
she wrote this weird poem and then she's like,
oh, that was about you and she was crying.
And then I felt really bad.
And then like the next day she was like, all mean.
And she's like, well, that poem wasn't about you.
That was about my ex-boyfriend.
She's like, why would I write that poem about you?
You know, I was like, well, I know you are not,
but it's like, you're you.
Well, then why did she say that?
I know, she said it was for me.
Like that, and it's like, so I was like, huh,
but it was always very skeptical when like people like,
It sounds like maybe it was and then she fucking maybe she's sobered up and she's like oh
I shouldn't have said that or whatever. I better I better say it was about someone else
She does that a lot
I mean I have the tape of it like where she her saying it like I have like
I mean it's because I watched it again just to make sure and like oh there
Yeah, she's like to get that thing on my wall was about you
You even have the clip of it. Oh my gosh. And then she says, Oh, I hate liars. I don't lie
But she fucking switches up all the time. That's crazy
People say like
You know, I had these like girls like when I was in like elementary school that would come prank my call prank my house and like say
Oh, you know, you're like they like me and stuff and then it's like, you know, if you react and it's like, oh, you stupid
And so I was like, I just have to say trauma from trial.
Like I remember this stuff, but like, and then it's like,
always been like, I've always been skeptical.
And so.
And I'm like, okay, we'll log out from under and like say,
leave Joe for something like that.
And then she did.
I was like, okay, well, I don't know.
I get attached to people also.
I'm very loyal to people and I don't stop loving people,
but it's like, just like how little she cares
and stuff like that.
And it's like, but now it's like,
now Alex is mad at me too.
Like, we're like-
What? Why?
Because like Carl, you know,
I was like, I got into it with Carl today in the check
because Carl was a bit on my show.
few times and like I heard sort of stories like, you know, but he's a narcissist to me
and like, so I ended up, I was like, I said he was a narcissist and that, you know, he's
still in love with Bea because it seemed like he was, and she's like, oh, you're jealous
and like, you know, you'd need to calm down in the chat and like, don't attack. And I was like,
wow, that's because I was like, I don't want to talk in private about it. I was like, okay.
Why he likes Carl, that Carl guy?
Yeah, I mean, it's okay. She does. I mean he's a silver Fox. He's a good-looking guy, right? But I don't know
Around the area like why'd he poke you back in like the panel verse because he's been gone for several months
And then he comes back and he goes back to my show runs to beat a show and then set her slanner hurts
I could be there's so many things that just happen again and again and again
So I just like either fancy the pattern or beauty itself. Okay, but
Yeah, it's just weird like
I hope, but I hope I can work out with her, but then also she thinks like, you know, she got a death threat on Bita's panel, like last night by Joe, but you know, Joe, she really is, but there's this guy.
thing that is and it's like and then he kind of had a blank stare when like Joe
said that and so now she think and they got the thing that is guys on my show
and so she thinks that like you know I'm hanging out with evil people like in
that he was like controlling Joe to say that something like that I don't know
exactly what she was but um she just like
But I think it would maybe or maybe society's entertaining, but I know it's why I don't know
Okay, who's back? Do you want to have the same man again or no? I don't bring him on if you don't want it
Talking about it doesn't matter to me because yeah, he doesn't know what he's talking about
But I mean I'll bring him back up one more time
But then if you don't want I'm here to say well, that's why I came on because I just got sick of listening to him spout
Come on here and use your channel to spot lies about me. Tell me just tell me to kick him if you want me to kick him
I know okay, it's crazy. You complain about you getting clapped with money. You kicking me with no money
And you just kicking me out just like a hubbub.
If you don't want to shut up and you just want to argue with me.
Calm down.
Stop getting it.
Nigga, go wash your ass.
Relax.
Go wash your ass.
I mean, jeez, how do you know I don't want to?
Wash your ass, my nigga.
Calm the fuck down.
Shut the fuck up.
I'll complain to you, bitch-ass nigga.
Yeah
Yeah, what the fuck I'm not kissing your ass to be on this panel fuck you bitch ass nigga
Fuck out of here nigga. I'm at the kids in your ass like I'm not these niggas nigga
Yeah, so what up, nigga
Trisha Trisha nigga, I don't kiss eyes Trisha. You're her. No, you're just a slimy snake in the grass
You glaze you look how you glaze Alex now Trisha after she did all that shit to you
Just like you glaze big T now remember now you glaze big T you glaze all your ops now
Why don't you let Psyche speak? It's his own fucking battle. You're so annoying.
No wonder he kicks you, you stupid ass.
Ooh, nigga. You think people watch you, Trisha? Or Psyche? No.
I'll go laugh and play music get more views.
I was like I play music and I had plenty of views.
I think you do.
Oh, so it's gone on me. Yeah. Just like a oh, I thought you hay faggots. He was begging you
Talking about how she raises fucking
You add your little fucking bitch in a bar
You just call my daughter a little bit
Watch your words
She can't even have a kid though
She's mad
When she called y'all PDF
Yeah
Show us your litter box. Yeah, we got the content was your little box. I mean we got the wiki. Don't worry
It's your litter box. We got the wiki now if you're fucking wife's fucking litter box
So is the M's shows the M's how long it takes to fix a phone
How long it takes to fix the phone?
You can fix
You could fix
Easy a hundred dollars
Why you can't fix the phone fix your phone
We waited on the phone
This is clipped already
No, nobody's gonna have to make a young man's pussy nigga
That is his pussy go around with think our road that word oh nigga with paperwork niggas writing with take our out clumsy
You play games with that guy
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
everyone. Well, you're, you're
playing video games with
how would you feel if I posted
that video of you getting out
the shower with good times?
I got that. I got that.
I got that. It was a joke. I
You got something that was
illegally. Yeah, you're
you got your noons,
I got that from you, Sammy.
I got your discord, Sammy.
Shout out to your discourse
No clip it nobody got new to crystal Marie niggas stupid
Yeah, I got it from your discord your discord. We got it. You're discord. Wow
You laughing nobody believes
We got it crystal
We still a yeah, let's see
Let's see black
Little clumsy, you know crystal Marie a clumsy set BG is grooming
Benny Blanco site been over there talking to Benny Blanco. We got to cover that too
Oops
I got exposed in the schools are weirdos Alex was right about y'all
You saw your mind you saw you saw your mind and family members for good time. Minor by the way. Minor by the way. Hey, we got the love nigga.
Keep on saying me. I love it. I love it. I love it. You got all my I got all my clips. I got everybody cooked. Y'all need to cook yourself.
Last night pussy. That's why you have. No we got it nigga.
I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you, I exposed you
You're going to miss that content.
I'm going to be a groomer.
Do you like seeing people groom them?
See where their mark is.
Is that what it is?
Is that why you're mad?
That crazy pathetic cunt.
Thank you.
Oh, you can't put it up. Oh, you know, he put it up. I ain't playin' it. This is a panel. It's important to think about that.
Yeah, he's playin' it. I'm not playin' it up. No, he ain't playin' it up for you.
Yeah, he's not playin' it for me.
Yeah, what happened?
Look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the side, look at the
the box. There's only one.
I didn't give me a fart.
You know, it's like, yeah, I don't mean it, but I've been a bad one.
What the fuck up you fucking drunk bitch?
You don't have a baby.
Drunk bitch?
You drinking through heroin now?
Yeah, I forgot.
Imagine that.
You through heroin.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, Ali?
I forgive you, Ali.
I forgive you.
Even though you come through.
I'm a child trafficker.
We got the love.
We got it, baby.
Sorry.
He's trying to bait me and say something bad about his miscarriage.
Don't talk about that, Christu, even though it's a lie.
Don't even talk about that.
I thought it didn't happen, man.
It's a lie. Don't talk about that.
It's a lie. It's a lie.
You don't hear me? It's a lie.
Don't talk about it.
He's going to say, you doing the same thing as them.
Let clumsy crash out.
Let clumsy talk about his death.
You don't have to match with any people.
He's a fucking widow.
He's a widow.
He's like your mama, you got no mama nigga.
You got no mama nigga.
I don't care.
I'm not crying.
You cryin' about it.
You got to be me cryin' about it.
You're on the panel with a faggot.
You said that is a faggot.
Now you're on the panel arguing with me.
Oh he's a faggot now.
Oh.
You said that.
He's a faggot.
Oh, I don't have to get psych ass to get on the panel
That's the problem clumsy. I don't have to kiss his ass to be on the panel you fucking dumbass
I don't have to suck his dick nigga like you
You had to be
I imagine I'm magic
Be cool with him nigga. I would never do that. Yeah, yeah, just like you said you hated faggots and now you're on sights
Yeah, so
You got a wannabe black man above you bro wanna be black man. Yeah
You fuckin' Mexican. You're the most laziest Mexican.
You're the most laziest Mexican.
No work, no job, no work, no job.
You just want to be online.
You want to be on YouTube with family.
No work, no job.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh
Yeah, you want to blame you want to blame people for what Alex did to him. That's the sad part Chris Murray
Alex did that to him. The New York guy
Whatever happened to him
Well
and they were both 14, 15, 16, which one, which one?
I would say that to come here.
I would say that about come here.
And you were like, how much would you pay for him?
How much would you pay for him?
Psyche, you asshole.
Damn.
But guess what, Chris and Marie, your husband hit me up, too.
Your husband hit me up, too.
And he joked about it, Chris.
So he said, yeah, I'm selling her.
I'm selling her how much you want.
He was joking about it, Chris and Marie.
You're wife gave me up
Yeah, it was gross
Remember
All right, yo salutes. All right. Shout out to the country. I did enough
Well, I'm I've got the content nigga. I've got please come eat. I've got treasure. I've got treasure
Yeah, so to the country, yo
Serves I'll be
I'll be live soon. Yeah
Fuck the word oh Trisha is lying
Out to the back up about you. Yeah, I'll be live soon. We ought to hear
You still fuck me over you guys are fucking crazy
Close for another older man
Sike, they don't listen to you, you know that, right?
You're calling me names last time.
You're a doddy.
No, shut up.
You're a doddy, you little fucking degenerate.
You got it.
You got to whip these slurs in line.
I can't even say you're fucking slurred.
You better act like him
I lose this fucking bit so you motherfuckers don't really think I'm an Arab dude cuz I'm like I'm kind of getting sick this shit
Thank you, you're the new Jerry Springer like you know that no matter how high brow you want to be and you can be
You're the Jerry Springer
And I like I have a racist fetish. You can call me all kinds of names
A lot of you degenerates are into that. I am. Call me F-A-G-G-O-T. I'll call you the book.
But I can't say if I call you F-A-G-G-O-T. I can't say N-I-G-G-E-R
Well, unless you refer it to me like that. Where'd you go?
Can I call you an F slur and slur?
Only in bed.
We're not psyche you can do better than me and I could do better. Let's be honest
We can get something younger
I'll say it to you one time right fucking now psyche little faggot ass
You little faggot ass nigga. You better buy you little booty pirate. There you go. You got it. I called you an ensler
You are the one bringing the entertainment the other sub-saharan african here cuz that was cool cuz dude
I think I've heard that guy before and he you cannot talk to him
He just yells over everybody and there was some white asshole that was like that niggas hole. Sorry. It was yeah
Okay, okay. I'm a shala. Yeah. Yeah, whatever the fuck. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah kumbaya is a fuck
I have a boner now, I really don't.
Yeah, it's hard to get a conversation.
Say it again, just say it to me, look at my eyes, one time.
You're a little faggot ass nigga, you little nigga.
I want to leave you like fucking him a tell.
It's enough, it's enough, it's enough.
You little hum.
Oh, OK.
I thought we were getting into this.
I can't, I can't.
You can do better than me.
You can get some young little twink home.
You know what?
I don't want a twink, I want a big masculine Viking like you.
Ew, no, I'm not big, I'm not masculine.
I'm I'm very not masculine. You have no idea like no you have no idea. I just I'm
Well, I would do that yeah, I think I should be used for that. I think that's my only life
If I can't do it to enslares then like there's no fucking point doing it
But anyway, yeah, you're a degenerate, but you should still impregnate a woman just to have progeny
Are you drinking so is he using drugs?
Alright
are you don't make me a Perry the fairy motherfucker you don't want to know about
Perry you don't want to know about the severed giant nigga penises
Hey, it's like I'm gonna go and jump off man. I'm gonna get ready for the day. I appreciate you
Comes he's a great guest, please come back
Tell me I'm not the only fucking dickhead on this show. Oh, Jesus. What's up, man?
What are you on mate? What the fuck are you doing? Like people are watching your muscles. Look at those arms
There's not mine. They haven't worked out
I'm old and ugly and short and
I'm a few years younger than you but still don't you want
Okay, what happens all you know you get all these hot women on here
And I think some of them
Psychic what the fuck mate like you know that like not just with my beliefs and stuff that because I'm not
Well, that's true. Yeah, okay, so now so now we're getting to a topic here. We're getting to nihilism right we're getting to
Like there's meaning and like, you know good butt sex. No wait
I guess for you. Okay, then you're then you're a butt
Okay, you know, it's freaking me out. Yeah, I was on my Nazi telegram
Even though I support Israel now because I hate the camel shits. It's a whole thing. I hated all Jews for seven years
I can't talk about that. I like half of them now like I hate half my own race. It's a whole thing. Anyway, so
Okay, yeah, I'll try to make this pal. They're flagging my videos down because the city ends slow all the time
I'm not gonna do it to you, but I'm saying I'm being
Also, okay, sorry girl
You're lucky. I'm drinking bitch because the bit of feminine and me is coming out against you
You deserve it
You're nice. You're not you actually don't deserve any of this. Who is that white asshole that kept paying money to come up here?
Some fat piece of shit. Did you kick him finally the ghosts or something?
Dude you're fucking Micah's way low hunt. Oh, it was funny that conductor
But that ghost asshole, I don't he never showed his fat face on
Tony a ghost is just one of his alter egos actually I like the ghost alter ego cuz that one
Well, he's too stupid to argue and he's that a hominem. I remember that from like a week or two ago
I know but the ghost is a bad arguer and Tony's not a very good arguer
But he has a character named Milton who's like brilliant if the only comes out once I think Perry would slay Milton
He is Perry too. Yeah, I know you don't understand
Okay, you don't understand because Perry the fairy is actually predicated on a real person that I knew
What I what? That's it's it's based on a person. It's based on a first. Sorry
What are you on nigga, what the fuck? Sorry
By Ellie's that it I love it dude. What is it?
Look if you're on opioid when you're not you know, you're on fucking
Niggi you on meth don't call me the n-word
Slur if I get you on
You're not trans I
You stop with that that really creeps me out
Can you stop being a creepy homo, please like you're a nice guy can't because it's inseparable for me
All I get are Nazis or self-hating blacks. That's what I like. I want a Nazi guy
You want to join telegram of you my thing they'll fucking call you slurs all fucking day man
One of them will probably give anyway, like what are you are you on something? Are you okay for real dude?
I'm fine, but please invite me to the telegram. It's not for because I'm racist. I just want to like
call that it's nothing but like dead ends and like dead ensalers all this yeah
yeah well it's I mean if you're pro in your private chat if you message me like
I'll answer I'll answer the phone I'll put it to you that way I don't have your
number like don't publish what if we get drunk we get drunk one night and then
you wake up and I'm s-ing your D put it that way
And then you're like, okay, this is like psyche what would you do? I just want to know like
I probably flip out and start kicking you in the face dude. Like don't do that like no
In a booth do it to some good when you're barefoot. I'm gonna hear this more
You were losing it. What's your fucking chat saying cuz you're being morbid degenerate like
You know, I get good weird shit. Yeah, man, you're you're fucking on something
I don't know if I do. Well, maybe it's mr.
Is it you with a jar of your ass and a horse, I don't want to see it
Okay, well you spoiled it for everybody
Mr. Hands
I can't refresh the chat. What is it?
Nice
Two candles, one red, one black
We lit both and laughed at the pact
Mirror cracked, cards on the floor
Who's who you asked?
I'm not sure anymore
You called me devil, I played the part
Charming
What the fool released in both whist
Collections that switch side
That was it, I'm sorry. There you go. Do you like it?
Remove it. There you go. I can't unmute wait
Are you doing it shoot?
You're talking about your shoot to me. Can I give you a package a special delivery of your shoot?
I mean you asked for it by the name really
No, I can't hear you. It's okay. You're sexy when you don't have a voice. Just move your hair around a little bit. Yes. Oh, fuck yeah
Always hot. Isn't he hot guys? I mean it's like I'm so I'm so I'm like really like
Embarrassed that I'm such a like, you know, wait, so you see your microphone is off honey. I need one
He's cute though. Yeah, but he's cute. Anyway, are you guys happy you stayed?
Hope you like the song. Oh, what is this song? What is what is that?
Excuse me. Hello. What is that? You're I don't like that. I don't like your name. Go go away
You're you can get out of the chat for a while
Okay, well you're all confused just get on your knees and and make me happy. I mean, what a dick
What is it? What do you think I've done is that was offensive to everybody
You might have to wrap up soon before this
My show gets reported to the FBI.
So let me see.
Thanks for sticking with me tonight, though, guys.
It's been fun, right?
It's been a barrel of
laughs.
my fire no i don't create it but i light it step into my storm no i won't fight it i'll ignite it
keep it strange divine no morning after no rewind this feels like a glitch in fate we don't
Be the kind of soul you can only touch in the astral
Yeah, we don't ride waves, we become the tidal
Call it devotion, maybe we should drown
I'm too far gone in nights like this
You don't need to call in sick
You're already inside the mystic
Call it devotion
Maybe we should drop emotion
I can be your vice, your omen
You're not the only one who's chosen
hey bang up you have to listen to one more thing then i'll stop i can't i can't stop until i do it though
That was a, I don't know, I'm not gonna bother with you anymore.
Are you mad at me?
You're gonna call me the name? I can't hear you, my love.
My love, I can't hear you, your microphone.
Nope. My love, you need to replace your microphone.
You look so cute though when you're talking like that.
What do you think, chat? Do you have a love connection? I don't hear you, love.
He's saying I love you guys. I think he's funny. What if he was finally saying he loves me, but I couldn't hear him
I couldn't hear him say it. He's saying he loves me. Look, I can see him in his lips. I
Love you dumb bag. Oh my god. Hey
Okay, oh no, just can you just flex for me? I don't care if you can talk or not
I just want to see you flex. You just flex a few times. Show me those arms. Take off your shirt if you can
Hello
Revalor read. I'm talking right to you. I can't hear you, but can I like can you just flex and take off your shirt and just like show me that?
body
And I can't hear you. He's saying really nice things that I can read lips. I think he's saying I love you psyche
Psychi will you come to Kentucky and marry me?
Psychi, I'm attracted to you and I think that you're really cool
Thank you. I want to fuck you. Oh my god. I want to fuck your ass. Oh my god
Yeah, I'm reviled red. I think you have to come back later because it's a little bit too much for my show right now
I can read lips. Okay. I know I hope you know you can read lips
You guys you guys thought you right? Oh
Gosh
Yeah, he's in love. Oh
Hey stargazer come on in
Sorry guys, we're just hanging out. I kicked off the the oh my god
He's putting on a he's getting naked and putting on a clan a clan outfit in the back my clown a clan
Why are you putting that? I don't like you know take off the hood. Oh, yeah
Okay, turn around. Oh
He's doing it guys. Okay. I love this guy. I'll try to see the microphone working out it worked yet
No, oh my god. He's he's saying. Oh my god psyche. I want to
Well, you know you want to do what Ruvaila? Oh
Cad
You want to do right? Yeah, you want to oh my gosh put it all the way in. Oh my god
You want me to do that to you?
He said it's for said he wants me to do that to him
Okay, oh you want to hear another song. Oh you do?
Okay, sure. Yeah, it's probably best I play one way you put on your audio to or you know, please your audio
Okay, perfect
Here's a raw wild anthem dry
Let's see how about this one reviler. Yeah, you're not in your head. Yes
Yeah, we already played that one can we play something play a different one? Yeah, okay
Sure. Okay.
This one's you.
They only haven't played Reviler.
Oh, because you're controlling the computer now, right?
You're in my house, right?
Where'd it go?
I got a keyboard army, but no paycheck yet.
Sending pizza, scrap man, manure at the door.
or just to get some coffee and stuff.
One more thing.
That's it. Yeah, okay.
I have one more.
I'll leave the stream on,
and I'll come back when I have coffee.
Otherwise...
I'm just a ghost in the livestream
Like, you think I'm mean, or you think people just mean I'm mean, she's so mean, she's so mean, you'll never even like, you know,
Her security's very tight, let's say, but
The rumors of me being Satan are highly exaggerated, but I wasn't frightened
So why are the bar up at 16 people at the table watching, you know, 16 people, I'm finally like talking, you know what I'm talking about, okay.
I see how it is. Oh yeah, I'm going to get bagels. I should get some breakfast guys.
Six cheese bagel. I'm going to try the cream cheese side of hash browns.
And the coffee in the cream.
like a plan they're not going anywhere until someone talks if no one talks I'm
gonna put on another video I have a stargazer to say goodbye like 20 minutes
ago it's been like literally 16 plus 10 minutes is the stream off or something I
know I got suspended because I was playing too much copyright so my dad
okay I got in trouble hello hello I feel like there's like 16 people to say
There's like standing and watching me there's like probably like 16 people that don't like me very much anymore. Hi guys
As you're here, like I probably do so love you
You decide to like just come in like look at me
I'd say a word like 16 people is a lot. That's like
No, there's like sports teams with less people on the team, right? It's like trying to football teams
in my bushes, literally in my bushes.
But anyway, well, okay.
You're asking for it, okay?
Are you asking for it?
She asked you nice.
If she was asking for it.
Did she ask you twice?
Oh, I don't think this is a good thing for a long time.
Chanel.
So what does it say?
I can't hold the 10 videos at the time.
Okay, I gotcha.
I'm gonna need to turn off.
Oh, that's why I can't get in the chat,
because I have all 10 things open.
Okay, guys, the chat is open.
Good morning.
Yeah, I won't fell asleep because like no one was talking at all at like 16 people in the room
Maybe I just have a relaxing voice or they like the music. Oh my god. I had all 10 things open
Oh my god, no wonder. Yeah
Ravila, I'm sorry
They didn't cute though, and he was when he was saying all those nice things to me
I really like that. I really enjoyed having him on the show Ravila red, right?
There we go
Hold on
Yeah
Crumble like a cookie when the heat's on stage
It's still us sitting in the cage
Talk tough online, but the flavor don't last
Snap like a cracker when the panel talks fast
Hook, beat us biscuits, dry and blend
No butter, no jam, just dust in your hand
Claim you bring spice, but you bring in regret
Panel got receipts, we ain't finished yet
You came to the kitchen, but forgot the recipe
Serving up crumbs while I feast on legacy
On the fire in the oven, you the smoke that won't stick
can't finish yet.
You're the snack that i-
Thanks for watching!
Let's lay the dead
Chaos, it's part of the game Secrets unravel, the stage is alive
In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive Who's awake?
We're awake, who's afraid Let it break, from shadows to starlight
The truth will be shown The Psyche awakens, you're never alone
Strange and unusual, step inside the flow
The circus of shadows, it's Psyche's show
Terrible trolls in the dark, take their stand, but angel
Saiki shi-
what the fuck you're still doing up you're still streaming it's sunday morning sunday morning
you just stay up all night like a vampire look at my skin are you looking at a vampire
you're in the light we both won't shut up shut up my light i'm not a light on this is my natural
skin tone it's just bright it's bright yeah it is
I'm going to bed.
You're going to go to bed?
Yeah, I have to go to bed.
All the way to show me that, but we
could finally have a microphone working.
Are you going to do a flex?
It was the fucking, the $1,200 pramp.
I just don't know.
You get to do a flex show for me.
Take off your white beards and do a flex one time.
No, please, no.
But never come on the show again.
Get, OK.
Really, dude?
You can never come on again.
You have to just talk one time.
You're crazy.
You need to stop doing drugs on me.
I want to see you.
You need to stop doing drugs, bro.
I may say never, but you need to stop doing drugs, brother.
Bye, girl.
He's probably my best hope for love.
And that's sad.
I mean, I feel bad for myself, like.
Yes, I don't know.
Um, okay, so I'm going to eat breakfast, right?
What should I do when I'm in breakfast?
Like, what should I do with the chat?
I'm trying to think.
You guys want to stay here? Let me see. Oh 16 people so maybe not
No, oh a what psyche awakens I'm biggest fan. Would you say that me?
That's why I'm going to get coffee and a bunch of food right now.
I don't like McDonald's breakfast though. McDonald's breakfasts are just janky, but you know what? They're like the
Einstein bagels, which is just I always have the I have the app though, right?
I'm sorry, I'm not talking loud enough. Where am I?
Right by Tyler, but he by Tyler read he did come by to say good night to me. I mean that was kind of romantic, right?
It was a little bit romantic, like
I think there's some potential there. I really do just have to like you know talk them into it more
But guys you feel bad like if I like hit on him
Is that like am I allowed to hit on him like I think he's in his 30s. I'm like, yeah, he's like
And he's like, you know
Very racist and I mean, so it's like is that okay if I hit on him
That's not gonna get everyone's opinion. Should I join their poll?
How many I wonder how many people said I should just go with how most of Polar's will I just look at player
Okay, where's the focus this big?
You have a couple beers or the mic's hard-loominated pretty good. Oh
My god, I said are you enjoying this app? And I'm your biggest fan and that reminds me of
Somebody I know let me see so every time they have a free coffee you can get you just edit the cart
Oh, okay location the store is closed for the day
For the day
Let's say or for later did what dates. Oh my gosh, you can't open a Sunday morning. I
Don't want to order
Dolls now
Okay, I'm gonna leave. I'm gonna leave because no one's talking to me
Like we're gonna sit here and talk to myself like some chooch. I just got the
Short bus, I mean, no
Okay, we'll have a good day guys. Oh
Go fuck yourself by the red fucking
Have peace of you.
Golden wings glowed in the candlelight
Crowds came running just to see the flame
But envy was the price of fame
And now he stands where the echoes fall
With tarot in hand hearing every call
From praise to venom in the same breath said
But the fire in his eyes burns gold